<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ubucon Asia 2021</title>
    <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ubucon Asia 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 10:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://2021.ubucon.asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>*No sessions yet</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/no-sessions-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 10:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/no-sessions-yet/</guid>
      <description>We don&amp;rsquo;t have any scheduled sessions and schedules for calling for papers yet. Notice for CFPs and session informations will be updated later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for organizers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 01:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers/</guid>
      <description>In Asia, You can find various community conferences about open source and linux that covers Asia region. Good examples of this are:
 openSUSE.Asia GNOME.Asia LibreOffice Asia Conference PyCon APAC FOSSASIA Summit and more&amp;hellip;  For past a few years, when I was the leader of Ubuntu Korea Community, I attended several conferences overseas to not just meet and learn but also to interact with Ubuntu local communities overseas. Especially, communities located near South Korea region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Ubucon Asia 2021</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome, and thank you for your interest on Ubucon Asia.
Ubucon Asia is an event organized by Ubuntu Communities in Asia. It&amp;rsquo;s for everyone who involved with or interested in Ubuntu, Linux and other Free and Open source technologies. Ubucon Asia is also a place for Ubuntu people from Asia to connect, learn, and share their knowlegdes each other.
Ubucon Asia 2021, the first Ubuntu conference in Asia will be a virtual conference driven by multiple Ubuntu LoCos from Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a sponsor</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your interest in Ubuntu and Ubucon Asia.
For this moment, We don&amp;rsquo;t have any plans for gathering sponsors yet.
Once we got details for sponsorship, We&amp;rsquo;ll post on this website.
If you have any questions, feel free to contact and ask by email sponsorship@ubucon.asia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenStack Indonesia Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/openstack-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/openstack-id/</guid>
      <description>OpenStack Indonesia (OS-ID) is an official OpenStack community (under Open Infrastructure Foundation) based in Indonesia. This community was established for all Indonesians who are interested in OpenStack projects/services.
In 2019, we held the first official community meetup in Jakarta and repeated monthly in several cities around Indonesia. First Indonesia Open Infrastructure Day was successfully held in November 2019 in Surabaya, and Last 2020 held the Open Infrastructure Day Indonesia event virtually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Korea Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-kr/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Korea Community is an official verified LoCo(Local Community) Team by Ubuntu Community Council in South Korea.
The Ubuntu Korean community started in 2005, very small. But it&amp;rsquo;s now one of the most active Open Source communities in South Korea. We are continuing to carry out activities that can be helpful to Ubuntu users in Korea and broadly to people related to IT in Korea.
We hold various seminars, conferences, community-driven projects, joint seminars with other communities, and contribution workshops every year, and we also exchange with various overseas open source communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Myanmar Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-mm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-mm/</guid>
      <description>Note: Due to this local community&amp;rsquo;s country level situation, Ubuntu Myanmar Community is volunteering only when they have some chance to participate.
 We, Ubuntu Myanmar Loco team is an Ubuntu Council-recognized Loco Team that is offering support in the ease use of Ubuntu Operating System in computers across Myanmar.
Ubuntu for Myanmar initiated action in 2009. It was a youth organization that had been continuously organizing Ubuntu and Ubuntu-related Open Source software events, free workshops and had been an active organization.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
