<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ubucon Asia 2021</title>
    <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ubucon Asia 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:45:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://2021.ubucon.asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>GNOME.Asia Summit 2021 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/gnomeasia_summit_2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/gnomeasia_summit_2021/</guid>
      <description>GNOME.Asia Summit 2021 hosted by Malaysia people will be on upcoming November! Learn some details about the event on this short session!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Organize Virtual Event with Open Source Tools 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/organize_virtual_event_with_open_source_tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/organize_virtual_event_with_open_source_tools/</guid>
      <description>This talk aims to enable community organizers to organize event with open source tools focusing on Eventyay and open source video solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing Integration Test with WSL APIs 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/developing_integration_test_with_wsl_apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 18:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/developing_integration_test_with_wsl_apis/</guid>
      <description>This session delivers how you can develop your own integration-test environment build tool with the WSL SDK project. WSL SDK project is an open-source project that provides versatile and robust WSL management APIs without any restrictions.
Also, I will share how I overcame technical hurdles with this project. If you are interested in the Win32 native programming aspect, you may obtain some insights from my talk.
About the speaker  Annual Microsoft MVP Award since 2009 WSLHUB, .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Closer with Kelompok Linux Arek Suroboyo and Buaya Linux Repository Server 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/getting_closer_with_kelompok_linux_arek_suroboyo_and_buaya_linux_repository_server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/getting_closer_with_kelompok_linux_arek_suroboyo_and_buaya_linux_repository_server/</guid>
      <description>Kelompok Linux Arek Suroboyo is a community of Linux users based in Surabaya. This community was formed in 1995 by a group of information technology activists in Surabaya. Because of concern for open source software products in Surabaya. In its development, many ups and downs occurred in the community camp as well as on the way to introducing the city of Surabaya to information and communication technology in the field of open-source software.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Having fun with Flutter Desktop development 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/having_fun_with_flutter_desktop_development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/having_fun_with_flutter_desktop_development/</guid>
      <description>Google and Canonical annouced Flutter support for Linux recently but have you wondered what exactly is Flutter? Why is it everywhere lately? Where can it run and is it easy to write apps in it? If you want to know more what is possible with Flutter and how it differs from other UI frameworks, join this session.
About the speaker I am programming Flutter from its early stages. Active member of London Flutter Community.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OEM metapackages &amp; Concourse CI 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/oem_metapackages__concourse_ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/oem_metapackages__concourse_ci/</guid>
      <description>What are OEM metapackages?What is Concourse CI?How to use Concourse CI on OEM metapackages?
https://hackmd.io/@fourdollars/oem-metapackages-and-concourse-ci#/
About the speaker Debian Developer / Ubuntu Contributing Developer / GNOME Emeritus Member / Canonical Employee</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Private Lab Virtualization Using Multipass and Deploy Apps web-based on Ubuntu Server. 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/private_lab_virtualization_using_multipass_and_deploy_apps_web_based_on_ubuntu_server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/private_lab_virtualization_using_multipass_and_deploy_apps_web_based_on_ubuntu_server/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Multipass is a virtualization product from Ubuntu that we can use to create a virtual machine and support cloud-init like in a public cloud. Multipass can be run in a local environment for free and is very suitable for development.
Here are some discussion points:  Reasons to use Multipass Advantages and Disadvantages of Multipass How to install Multipass How to use Multipass and basic commands in Multipass Basic Cloud-init Install web-based applications demonstration on VMs Multipass Additional material on Multipass integration  About the speaker Village child who like to learn Open Source, Linux, and Cloud Computing and become the Founder of BelajarLinux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The challenge of Using LibreOffice &amp; Building Local Community in Korea 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/the_challenge_of_using_libreoffice__building_local_community_in_korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/the_challenge_of_using_libreoffice__building_local_community_in_korea/</guid>
      <description>In South Korea, Both HWPML(file format: hwp) and ODF are a Document format standard as a public sector. The Republic of Korea government adopted OpenDocument as a part of Korean Industrial Standards KS X ISO/IEC 26300 in 2007.However, In South Korea&amp;rsquo;s academic field, the public &amp;amp; private sector, It is still using HWP as a document standard. They are still made and distributed in .hwp format. I&amp;rsquo;m a Full-time worker(Developer) &amp;amp; University student in Korea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mengetik Aksara Pegon dengan Ubuntu 20.04.2 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/mengetik_aksara_pegon_dengan_ubuntu_20042/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:10:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/mengetik_aksara_pegon_dengan_ubuntu_20042/</guid>
      <description>Menurut wikipedia, Pegon is an Arabic script used to write the Javanese, Madurese and Sundanese languages, as an alternative to the Latin script or the Javanese script.
Pada Ubuntu 20.04.2 belum tersedia Keyboard Pegon. Pegon merupakan penulisan abjad Jawa atau Sunda atau Indonesia menggunakan abjad Arab. Oleh karena itu sebagian besar karakter Pegon sudah tersedia pada blok Unicode Arab.
Di MTs Irsyaduth Thullab, soal cbt mata pelajaran kitab kuning ditulis dengan aksara Pegon walau dengan berbagai kendala seperti;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If you need LAMP Stack, Journey to Ubuntu with WSL2 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/if_you_need_lamp_stack_journey_to_ubuntu_with_wsl2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/if_you_need_lamp_stack_journey_to_ubuntu_with_wsl2/</guid>
      <description>I needed LAMP Stack for working with Wordpress. I&amp;rsquo;m not a developer or software engineer. and I just had only one small laptop. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use public cloud for security. So, I fell in love with WSL2. At first, I was a little hard to set. but, It was not so hard to drive. Let me show you, how I started setting ubuntu with WSL2 For beginers.
About the speaker Life is just TEST.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>openEuler社区的开源合规实践(Open source compliance practice of the openEuler community) 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/openeuleropen_source_compliance_practice_of_the_openeuler_community/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/openeuleropen_source_compliance_practice_of_the_openeuler_community/</guid>
      <description>openEuler通过社区合作，打造创新平台，构建支持多处理架构、统一和开放的操作系统，推动软硬件应用生态繁荣发展。 openEuler is an innovative platform nurtured by community collaboration. It aims to build a unified and open OS that supports multiple processor architectures, and to advance the hardware/software application ecosystem. openEuler社区在开源合规方面还不是很成熟，但已经努力摸索出一条有自己特色的发展之路，希望借助UbuCon Asia 2021这个平台与更多的开源伙伴交流促进。 OpenEuler community is not very mature in terms of open source compliance, but it has worked hard to find a development path with its own characteristics, hoping to use the platform of UbuCon Asia 2021 to communicate with more open source partners.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using kexec to speed-up reboot 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/using_kexec_to_speed_up_reboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 16:55:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/using_kexec_to_speed_up_reboot/</guid>
      <description>kexec loads a new kernel image without going through the hardware&amp;rsquo;s initialization stage, drastically speeding up the reboot process.
In this lightning talk, pros and cons of kexec will be listed along with how-to instructions on using kexec on Ubuntu 20.04.
We&amp;rsquo;re currently using kexec to speed up our development and successfully reduced the reboot time from 2 minutes to 10 seconds on a server machine.
About the speaker I&amp;rsquo;m a 23 years old student at DGIST DataLab, currently pursuing a Ph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction Indonesia Communities 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/introduction_indonesia_communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 16:50:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/introduction_indonesia_communities/</guid>
      <description>Introduction to Indonesia Communities</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu on Cloud Environments 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/ubuntu_on_cloud_environments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 16:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/ubuntu_on_cloud_environments/</guid>
      <description>Sponsored session (Cloudmate Co. Ltd.)
 In this session, we will discuss about how Ubuntu and other Linux are compatible to major Public Cloud Providers such as AWS, Azure, and GCP. We will also talk about what kind of images, services, subscriptions, and products are available from them.
About the speaker Sejun Kim  Orgenizer of &amp;ldquo;The AzureLife(애저로운 생활)&amp;rdquo; Microsoft Azure MVP Cloud Architect Cloudmate Technical Enginnering Leader.  Junhyeon Bae  Manager of Lead Engineering Team at Cloudmate Co.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Web Hosting Server using Ubuntu and Cyberpanel 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/web_hosting_server_using_ubuntu_and_cyberpanel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 15:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/web_hosting_server_using_ubuntu_and_cyberpanel/</guid>
      <description>In this material I will discuss cyberpanel on the ubuntu server that I use for daily web hosting at my office.CyberPanel is a web control panel that is directly supported by OpenLiteSpeed, with a number of other excellent features such as GIT Manager, Docker Manager, SSL, and others.
About the speaker Experienced System Administrator with a demonstrated history of working in the internet industry. Skilled in Network Administration, Server Administration, Computer Network Operations, Open Source Software, and Computer Repair.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>K8s - MicroK8s &amp; K3s 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/k8s___microk8s__k3s/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 15:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/k8s___microk8s__k3s/</guid>
      <description>MicroK8s High availability K8s Low-ops, minimal production Kubernetes, for devs, cloud, clusters, workstations, Edge and IoT.
 https://microk8s.io/  K3s Lightweight Kubernetes
 https://k3s.io/  About the speaker I have played around with Linux since 2004, from Web Designer to Web Administrator (For LAMP) with Ubuntu being my main choice. I settled on Ubuntu as my favourite Linux distro. I will Promote About Linux and Ubuntu Distro since 2009., Raspberry Pi since 2013, Container LXD at 2014, Open Stack at 2016, DevOps at 2018, Docker and Kubernetes at 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu OS &amp; Service patch management using Ansible 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/ubuntu_os__service_patch_management_using_ansible/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 15:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/ubuntu_os__service_patch_management_using_ansible/</guid>
      <description>To patch just one system, the administrator must identify that a patch is available, download it, and then deploy it to the system. In an enterprise environment, there could be hundreds of servers to manage, so the job of patch management becomes an all-day responsibility with the added risk of reboot fails after installation. Instead of manual updates, administrators can free up time and organize patches using automation tools.
Using Ansible made patch management simpler than ever.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating boring and repetitive UbuCon Asia video and subtitle stuffs 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/automating_boring_and_repetitive_ubucon_asia_video_and_subtitle_stuffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 14:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/automating_boring_and_repetitive_ubucon_asia_video_and_subtitle_stuffs/</guid>
      <description>Whether it&amp;rsquo;s online or offline event, There&amp;rsquo;s always boring and repetitive jobs for event organizers and volunteers. Putting cover on session videos and making subtitle for videos are part of them. UbuCon Asia team, is no exception. But like you and other ordinary people, our organizers also have their own job and busy with that usually. As it&amp;rsquo;s first event we don&amp;rsquo;t even know if we can gather enough volunteers or gain sponsorship to hire some workers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Judge A Book by Its Cover: Contributing to Open Source Communities with Graphic Design 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/dont_judge_a_book_by_its_cover_contributing_to_open_source_communities_with_graphic_design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 14:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/dont_judge_a_book_by_its_cover_contributing_to_open_source_communities_with_graphic_design/</guid>
      <description>In this digital era, everyone uses multimedia in their daily life. Cell phones, social media, and the internet seem to be the new basic needs. Moreover, the pandemic has increased the intensity of gadget use due to limited mobility and physical activity. Like it or not, all activities turn to online activities.
This makes business people, event organizers, and content creators compete for attention by displaying visuals and attractive appearances for each of their content.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Promote Ubuntu localization of the ethnic groups in China. 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/promote_ubuntu_localization_of_the_ethnic_groups_in_china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 13:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/promote_ubuntu_localization_of_the_ethnic_groups_in_china/</guid>
      <description>This talk is about how we process Chinese Tibetan localization in last year. It includes the huge translation management, open source community and university collaboration, and the localization status of other ethnic groups in China.
About the speaker Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Bugress Chang</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Snap in MicroOS 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/snap_in_microos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 13:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/snap_in_microos/</guid>
      <description>Snap in openSUSE MicroOS Desktop
According to openSUSE wiki, openSUSE MicroOS is an operating system you don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about. It&amp;rsquo;s designed for but not limited to container hosts and edge devices. openSUSE MicroOS Desktop is a MicroOS with a desktop-focused variant of MicroOS based on Tumbleweed. MicroOS Desktop is an immutable, rolling base as based on Tumbleweed.
Snaps are app packages for desktop, cloud, and IoT that are easy to install, secure, cross-platform, and dependency-free, developed by Canonical.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The input method, another way to edit Japenense documents, Hanjp project 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/the_input_method_another_way_to_edit_japenense_documents_hanjp_project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 13:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/the_input_method_another_way_to_edit_japenense_documents_hanjp_project/</guid>
      <description>In this session, I&amp;rsquo;d like to introduce about Hanjp Input Method project, first of all. Its concept, the reasons why did I start the project, current state, and some demos are included. Then, I will re-introduce it in techincal view. Choosen languages and libraries, program structure, and project milestone are included. Then lastly, I&amp;rsquo;d talk about community development. Current contribution activity, Open Up activities(the open source activity) are included. Please refer to URL below to get informed about Hanjp project https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UKUI3 Technology Sharing In Tablet Mode 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/ukui3_technology_sharing_in_tablet_mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 13:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/ukui3_technology_sharing_in_tablet_mode/</guid>
      <description>Ukui 3.0 is a lightweight desktop environment based on Linux release developed by Kylin team. In addition to the traditional desktop mode, the tablet mode is also provided to meet the needs of various scenarios.We will share ukui&amp;rsquo;s experience and achievements in how to add support for tablet form and its future planning.
About the speaker R &amp;amp; D Manager of UbuntuKylin team</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social event - Day 1 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/social_event___day_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 19:25:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/social_event___day_1/</guid>
      <description>On Gather Town - TBD
TBD</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Panel Discussion - Open Source Communities in Asia: Opportunities and Challenges  
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/panel_discussion___open_source_communities_in_asia_opportunities_and_challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/panel_discussion___open_source_communities_in_asia_opportunities_and_challenges/</guid>
      <description>We will hear from representatives of our hosts and open source communities in Asia. https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/
Moderator: Hong Phuc Dang
Speakers: TBC
About the speakers Hong Phuc Dang Hong Phuc is the founder of FOSSASIA, an organization that strives to improve people’s lives through sharing open technologies and fostering global connections and sustainable production. She serves as a member of the IEEE Standards Association Board of Governors and as vice chair of the Open Source Committee.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Developing on Ubuntu with WSL Interoperability: Tips and Tricks 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/developing_on_ubuntu_with_wsl_interoperability_tips_and_tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 17:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/developing_on_ubuntu_with_wsl_interoperability_tips_and_tricks/</guid>
      <description>This session will provide the practical considerations of developing on Ubuntu on WSL with WSL interoperability, providing attendees a better understanding of WSL interoperability when developing on Ubuntu on WSL.
About the speaker Software Developer for Ubuntu on WSL and Ubuntu on Hyper-V, core maintainer for WSL Utilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Engaging new l10n contributors through Open Source Contributhon 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/engaging_new_l10n_contributors_through_open_source_contributhon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 17:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/engaging_new_l10n_contributors_through_open_source_contributhon/</guid>
      <description>Last year, Ubuntu Korean LoCo participated &amp;ldquo;Open Source Contributhon&amp;rdquo;(Contribution + Marathon) as Ubuntu Korean L10n team to engage new l10n contributors. &amp;ldquo;Open Source Contributhon&amp;rdquo; is an program led by a government agency, And more than 20 teams joined last year.
In this session, We&amp;rsquo;ll introduce details about &amp;ldquo;Open Source Contributhon&amp;rdquo;(which is now &amp;ldquo;Open Source Contribution Academy&amp;rdquo;) and our experiences about the program as mentors and as mentees.
Bokmi Han will introduce about the Open Source Contributhon program</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Survival of The Fittest: How Open-source Helps Me Survive after Company Shutdown 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/survival_of_the_fittest_how_open_source_helps_me_survive_after_company_shutdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 16:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/survival_of_the_fittest_how_open_source_helps_me_survive_after_company_shutdown/</guid>
      <description>A year ago, I was still actively working as a general manager in a tour &amp;amp; travel company. At the beginning of the pandemic, my company minimized activity and created new services to survive the pandemic. However, at the end of the day, we have to face the reality: we have to shut down the company because our company relies on mobility and physical activity which currently has to be limited.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hacking on Unity7 and UnityX 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/hacking_on_unity7_and_unityx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 16:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/hacking_on_unity7_and_unityx/</guid>
      <description>In this session, I’ll be demonstrating how to set up a build environment for Unity7. I’ll then be compiling It live. I’ll also be showing how to set up a build environment for UnityX. I’ll then fix some bugs in it and compile it live. I’ll also demonstrate how to do a Merge Request on GitLab and package it using qckdeb.
About the speaker I&amp;rsquo;m an official Ubuntu Member and the creator and project lead of Ubuntu Unity and Ubuntu Web Remix.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who &#39;kill&#39;ed my processes? 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/who_killed_my_processes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 15:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/who_killed_my_processes/</guid>
      <description>All of sudden, one of your processes that should be alive was &amp;lsquo;kill&amp;rsquo;ed by someone&amp;rsquo;s Signal! Who did that? Let&amp;rsquo;s trace the issue with Linux Kernel hacking. In this session, I will talk about a real-life issue I met while working and attendees would learn about where to start if they want to trace signals through Kernel.
Attendees at least should know what the Signal is in Computer Science.
About the speaker I had been contributing to GNOME foundation as a programmer for 2 years before and currently interested in ARM64 Linux Kernel core and Network Subsystem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CI/CD with Snap package deployment 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/cicd_with_snap_package_deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 15:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/cicd_with_snap_package_deployment/</guid>
      <description>Sponsored session (Ubuntu)
 Build, test and publish applications automatically. Bring CI/CD to your IoT andappliances. Give your developers a pipeline to deliver updates to customersstraight from their standard process, and empower customers to test beta andpre-release versions. Whether you’re using Git with Travis or Jenkins,automated snap creation is just a few steps away. For open source projects, wewill even build your snap for ARM, x86, POWER and Z. Canary updates and automaticrollbacks let you go fast with confidence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Desktop Ubutu on Laptops/RaspberryPis - practices how to use it with SD cards, how to manage UEFI and more 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/desktop_ubutu_on_laptopsraspberrypis___practices_how_to_use_it_with_sd_cards_how_to_manage_uefi_and_more/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 15:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/desktop_ubutu_on_laptopsraspberrypis___practices_how_to_use_it_with_sd_cards_how_to_manage_uefi_and_more/</guid>
      <description>Desktop Ubuntu is a good use for workstations and some games development. I have tried for it not only software/hardware development but also game and daily use. Lately, we can use Chinese hackable PCs like GPD/Chuwi, which encourages &amp;lsquo;hacking.&amp;rsquo; - Firmware/OSes. We could customize such PCs for our use.
I will talk and discuss about my practice to use Ubuntu Desktop on Raspberry Pi and such &amp;lsquo;hackable&amp;rsquo; PCs.
 How to treat SD cards.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Sinau Bash&#34; Program for Learning Bash Commands 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/sinau_bash_program_for_learning_bash_commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 14:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/sinau_bash_program_for_learning_bash_commands/</guid>
      <description>Bash is considered a difficult language for some people to learn. In general, bash language itself is used by people who work in the field of servers. People who work in the server field will be very helpful with the bash language because bash can run many commands on the server or can run commands automatically. For example, bash language is used in Ubuntu Server. In addition to the bash language server, it can be used in making programs, namely &amp;ldquo;Sinau Bash&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How Ubuntu empowers databases and cloud development on Azure 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/how_ubuntu_empowers_databases_and_cloud_development_on_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 14:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/how_ubuntu_empowers_databases_and_cloud_development_on_azure/</guid>
      <description>Sponsored Session (Microsoft)
 In this workshop, you will learn or ask your questions on how to deploy SQL Server on Linux 2019 and run a web application on a new Azure Linux virtual machine by following a great Microsoft Learn module: https://aka.ms/LearnAzureAtUbuConAsia.
Pre-requisites:
 Experience using Bash from the command-line Familiarity or interest in using JavaScript to connect a database and/or build web applications  Have you already finished this module?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keynote - Flutter for Linux 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/keynote___flutter_for_linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 13:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/keynote___flutter_for_linux/</guid>
      <description>The desktop team has spent a great deal of time working on Flutter, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the motivation to invest in Flutter, the current status and future plans.
About the speaker Ken VanDine is an Engineering Manager at Canonical, leading the Ubuntu Desktop team. Ken has been involved in open source for over 20 years and is passionate about helping new developers get involved in open source. In Ken&amp;rsquo;s spare time he volunteers at Kramden Institute, refurbishing computers for underprivileged children and teaching middle school-aged children how to code.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome and Opening Remarks 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/welcome_and_opening_remarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/welcome_and_opening_remarks/</guid>
      <description>This session will cover how and why we have organized the first UbuCon Asia event. We&amp;rsquo;ll also introduce our host organizing communities, sponsors and partner communities.
About the speaker  Community Leader and Organizer at Ubuntu Korea Community Junior DevOps Engineer at Cloudmate Studies Software engineering at Sungkonghoe University  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft has joined as a Gold Sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-08-microsoft-joins-as-gold-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 20:49:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-08-microsoft-joins-as-gold-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We are proud to announce Microsoft as a Gold Sponsor for Ubucon Asia 2021.
Microsoft requires no introduction in the technology world.
Azure cloud, hybrid cloud and on-premise technologies are leaders in software as a service (SaaS), platform as a service (PaaS) and infrastructure as a service (IaaS).
Did you know that Ubuntu-based workloads are among the fastest growing on Microsoft Azure? Their partnership with Canonical has delivered an Azure-optimized kernel, improved performance, advanced security, automatic patching and updates, and flexible pricing options for Ubuntu on Azure as well as open source communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Networking on Gather Town space</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-05-networking-on-gather-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 23:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-05-networking-on-gather-town/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone! The first UbuCon Asia coming in less then a month!
On this first UbuCon Asia, We&amp;rsquo;ll also have an additional virtual space: Gather Town space We&amp;rsquo;ll use both Eventyay and Gather Town.
 Eventyay for ticketing, timetable, video conference calls and Sponsor/Partner Community information page(Exhibition page) Gather Town space for Virtual booth(for sponsors and partner communities) and Networking between attendees!  Since we made decision on this very recently, Other then Virtual booth details, We don&amp;rsquo;t have plans on other details yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudmate joins as our Silver sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-08-10-cloudmate-joins-as-silver-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 01:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-08-10-cloudmate-joins-as-silver-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We are gladly to announce Cloudmate as our part of Silver Sponsor.
Cloudmate is an certified CSP(Cloud Service Provider) company in Seoul, South Korea. They provides professional managed service on cloud environment. Based on experiences from MNCs, Cloudmate has its best certified engineers and developers in the cloud sector. Through the professional managed service, Cloudmate supports systematic management and its cloud infrastructure to the customers. Furthermore, Cloudmate also offers consulting for cloud service to industries that are adapting cloud infrastructure for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello UbuCon Asia speakers!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-30-speaker-schedules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 12:47:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-30-speaker-schedules/</guid>
      <description>Hello UbuCon Asia 2021 speakers! Thanks again for submitting your proposals for the first UbuCon Asia! We just completed reviewing proposals and now reaching out each person to confirm speaker participation.
Confirm your participation If your proposal was accepted, We&amp;rsquo;ll send you an email to confirm whether you&amp;rsquo;ll give speech on the event. You may also check eventyay to see whether your proposal was accepted. To confirm your speaker participation, simply reply us and tell us you will participate as speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you to Ubuntu for Join as Diamond Sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-24-ubuntu-joins-as-diamond-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 01:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-24-ubuntu-joins-as-diamond-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We are gladly to announce Ubuntu as our part of Diamond Sponsor.
The Ubuntu desktop as we know is the world&amp;rsquo;s most widely used Linux workstation platform, powering the work of engineers across the globe. Ubuntu today has many flavours and dozens of specialized derivatives. All share common infrastructure and software, making Ubuntu a unique single platform that scales from consumer electronics to the desktop and up into the cloud for enterprise computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for speakers is now closed!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-15-cfs-is-now-closed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:22:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-15-cfs-is-now-closed/</guid>
      <description>Hello folks! Calling for speakers is now closed!
Thanks to everyone who submitted session proposals to the first Ubuntu conference in Asia! We have received total 46 proposals! This includes&amp;hellip;
 Talks &amp;amp; Extended Talks Lightning talks Workshops Panel discussions  But this does not includes social events and sponsor sessions yet. In next 2 weeks, Our content team will review your submissions until the end of this month. Content team folks may contact to each person who submitted proposals to ask some further details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double check your proposal submissions before deadline</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-11-double-check-proposal-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 15:34:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-11-double-check-proposal-submission/</guid>
      <description>Call for speakers will close soon on July 14th 23:59 UTC+9! If you have submitted any session proposals, please double check your submissions and update it if required before the deadline comes.
Your speaker info Please see the image and description below and check your speaker info submissions once again to see if anything missing.
 Name: Your full name (e.g. Youngbin Han) Email: Your email contact address. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive proposal review result with the email address you entered here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for proposals extended by July 14</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-30-cfp-extended-by-july-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 08:31:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-30-cfp-extended-by-july-14/</guid>
      <description>If you have been rush into submitting proposal, You now have extra 2 more weeks to finalize submitting your proposlas! UbuCon Asia 2021 Calling for proposal due date has been extended by July 14th 23:59 (UTC+9).
For your informations, See details you need know from below before submitting proposals. Please do not hesitate to contact Ubucon Asia team whether through social media or email if you are not sure about writing your proposal or preparing your presentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become our individual patron today</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-24-donation-ticket/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:20:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-24-donation-ticket/</guid>
      <description>To raise enough amount of money required stably, We&amp;rsquo;re announcing another way to contribute on our event. From today, You can contribute to our successful event by becoming one of our individual patrons!
To become our patron, Visit our event page on eventyay.com and follow steps below.
 Sign in with your eventyay.com account. Scroll down to &amp;ldquo;Tickets&amp;rdquo; section, You will see &amp;ldquo;Sign Up to Join Ubucon Asia 2021&amp;rdquo; which is free ticket and &amp;ldquo;Donation Ticket&amp;rdquo; Set price of donation ticket you would like to donate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Proposals</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-30-calling-for-proposals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:39:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-30-calling-for-proposals/</guid>
      <description>UbuCon Asia 2021 team have been calling for speakers, volunteers, sponsors and community partners from earlier this month. As this is the first time to organize UbuCon Asia, Our proposal period is relatively longer then other conferences. This is a reminder post that includes all details for each items and URL link to them.
Calling for speakers  Submit until June 30th 2021, Session acceptance will be on July 30th 2021 Session type: Talk(30min, 45min), Lightning talk(5min), Workshop(1hour, 2hour), Panel duscussions(55mins) All session duration includes time for question and answer For &amp;ldquo;Talk&amp;rdquo; type session, you can submit pre-recorded session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Video Translation Volunteers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-calling-for-translation-volunteers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 12:01:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-calling-for-translation-volunteers/</guid>
      <description>As we begin calling for speakers, We&amp;rsquo;re now also calling for translation volunteers from today. Translation volunteers will colloborate local community to translate pre-recorded sessions from following languages to English.
 Korean - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Korea Community Japanese - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Japanese Community Chinese(China) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu China Community Chinese(Taiwan) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Taiwan Community Cantonese(Hong Kong) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Hong Kong Community Indonesian - You will collaborate GNOME Indonesia and Openstack Indonesia  We will use speech-to-text and machine translation tool to automate subtitle works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Speakers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-call-for-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 09:50:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-call-for-speakers/</guid>
      <description>The first Ubuntu Conference in Asia (Ubucon Asia 2021) is four months ahead! Ubucon Asia 2021 Call for Speakers is now open until 30 June, and talks acceptance will be on 30 July.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the reference topics for you to discuss in Ubucon Asia 2021:
 Desktop Server/Infrastructure/Cloud Windows Subsystem for Linux(WSL) Localization(L10n)/Fonts/Input Methods Internet of Things(IoT)/Embedded Security Community/Social Context Case Studies etc.  We have some sessions to talk with two days event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubucon Asia 2021 Plan updates</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-04-21-some-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:10:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-04-21-some-updates/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been about 3 months after I published post &amp;ldquo;Looking for organizers&amp;rdquo;. Last 3 months, many Ubuntu Local communities and other FLOSS communities contact me to join Ubucon Asia 2021 team. Today, We have 12 host communities from 10 different regions in the team. Some organizers from those communities with excellent experience with organizing international events also joined our team.
And with this Ubucon Asia 2021 team, We&amp;rsquo;ve been made many progress until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for organizers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 01:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers/</guid>
      <description>In Asia, You can find various community conferences about open source and linux that covers Asia region. Good examples of this are:
 openSUSE.Asia GNOME.Asia LibreOffice Asia Conference PyCon APAC FOSSASIA Summit and more&amp;hellip;  For past a few years, when I was the leader of Ubuntu Korea Community, I attended several conferences overseas to not just meet and learn but also to interact with Ubuntu local communities overseas. Especially, communities located near South Korea region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>.NET DEV</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/dotnetdevkr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/dotnetdevkr/</guid>
      <description> .Net Dev is a local .Net user group in South Korea. Our community members are especially interested in .NET development and its ecosystem.  Including ASP.NET, EF, Blazor, etc&amp;hellip;   We runs regular local conference called &amp;ldquo;.NET Conf x Seoul&amp;rdquo; every year and &amp;ldquo;.NET Conf Mini&amp;rdquo; almost every quarter. .NET Conf Korea by .NET Dev: https://dotnetconf.kr .NET Medium Blog: https://blog.dotnetdev.kr .NET Dev Discourse: https://forum.dotnetdev.kr  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Ubucon Asia 2021</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome, and thank you for your interest on Ubucon Asia.
Ubucon Asia is an event organized by Ubuntu Communities in Asia. It&amp;rsquo;s for everyone who involved with or interested in Ubuntu, Linux and other Free and Open source technologies. Ubucon Asia is also a place for Ubuntu people from Asia to connect, learn, and share their knowlegdes each other.
Ubucon Asia 2021, the first Ubuntu conference in Asia will be a virtual conference driven by multiple Ubuntu LoCos from Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a sponsor</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your interest in Ubuntu and Ubucon Asia.
As a non-profit and community organized event, Even Ubucon Asia 2021 is fully virtual event, We still need support from sponsors to make the event happen.
By becoming one of our sponsors, you are directly contributing to research and development of Ubuntu and Open Source Software, and also making Open Source Community more active and sustainable.
Your contribution makes it possible for us to bring a large number of Ubuntu users and contributors across Asia to connect, interact, help and learn together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudmate</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/cloudmate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/cloudmate/</guid>
      <description>Cloudmate is the certified CSP company that located in Seoul, Korea.
Cloudmate provides professional managed service on cloud environment. Based on experiences from MNCs, Cloudmate has its best certified engineers and developers in the cloud sector. Through the professional managed service, Cloudmate supports systematic management and its cloud infrastructure to the customers. Furthermore, Cloudmate also offers consulting for cloud service to industries that are adapting cloud infrastructure for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debian Malaysia</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/debian-malaysia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/debian-malaysia/</guid>
      <description>Malaysian Debian GNU/Linux enthusiasts community
You can be reach us by various means:
 Chat: Telegram group (https://t.me/debianmalaysia) / IRC #debian-malaysia on Freenode / Matrix /join #freenode_#debian-malaysia:matrix.org Website: http://debianmalaysia.gitlab.io (mirror: https://malaysia-team.pages.debian.net) Mailing lists: Debmal google group (https://groups.google.com/g/debmal) Social media: Twitter - https://twitter.com/debianmalaysia / Mastodon - https://linuxrocks.online/@debianmalaysia (both cross-posted)  Please choose what ever communication channel and you are welcome!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSS Nepal Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/foss-np/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/foss-np/</guid>
      <description>FOSS Nepal Community is a team of volunteers who believe in the usage of Free/Open Source Software (FOSS). The primary objective of the community is to promote, develop and diversify the usage of Free/Open Source Software in Nepal.
 To raise awareness among general public, government bodies, private sector, civil society, educational institutions and media for expanding the scope of Information and Communication Technology (ICT) via Free and Open Source Software To sensitize general public, government bodies, civil society and media for the implementation of e-governance by means of FOSS; the optimal solution for e-governance Advocacy for alternatives in Intellectual Property Rights (IPR) specific to ICT To enhance the capacity of IT professionals by promoting inclusion of Free and Open Source Software in educational system and providing platform for IT professionals to make them globally saleable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSSASIA</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/fossasia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/fossasia/</guid>
      <description>FOSSASIA develops Open Source software and hardware solutions with a global developer community from its base in Asia and organizes Open Technology events around the year. The organization also runs coding programs and development contests.
The annual FOSSASIA Summit is the premier Open Technology event in Asia for developers, start-ups, and contributors. It is a unique opportunity to share knowledge and experience about Open Source and meet interesting contributors.
FOSSASIA was founded in 2009 by Mario Behling and Hong Phuc Dang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gimpscape ID</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/gimpscape-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/gimpscape-id/</guid>
      <description>Gimpscape ID community is a one of design community from Indonesia that has oriented to the use of Free/Open Source Software (FOSS). On various occasions, Gimpscape ID always strives to contribute to activities related to free/open source software.
 Telegram https://t.me/gimpscape Instagram https://instagram/gimpscape_id  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/gnome-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/gnome-id/</guid>
      <description>GNOME Indonesia (GNOME-ID) is a non-profit community founded to support the use, promotion and assistance of users of the GNOME desktop environment in Indonesia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join as Partner Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/join-as-partner-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/join-as-partner-community/</guid>
      <description>To promote UbuCon Asia event across Asia much further, We’re looking for partner communities. By becoming our partner community, Your community will collaborate with UbuCon Asia team to cross-promote each other’s community and event. This will be a big help for both partner communities and UbuCon Asia to connect with even more diverse people and encourage them to participate and engage.
To learn more about our partner community program, please refer to our brochure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KLAS (Kelompok Linux Arek Suroboyo)</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/klas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/klas/</guid>
      <description>Arek Suroboyo Linux Group (Surabaya Linux User Group) (KLAS) is one of the Linux user groups in the city of Surabaya. We have been around since 1995, and are still active today. We have several routine agendas and facilities that we do and until now we have facilitated them to support Go FOSS activities in Surabaya, such as:
 Cangkrukan KLAS Local Conferences (Open Infrastucture Day 2019) International Conferences (openSUSE.Asia Summit 2019, GNOME.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/microsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/microsoft/</guid>
      <description>Our mission is to empower every person and every organization on the planet to achieve more.
Ubuntu-based workloads are among the fastest growing on Azure. Microsoft has partnered with Canonical to deliver an Azure-optimized kernel, improved performance, advanced security, automatic patching and updates, and flexible pricing options for Ubuntu on Azure as well as open source communities.
Click here to learn more about Ubuntu on Azure</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenStack Indonesia Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/openstack-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/openstack-id/</guid>
      <description>OpenStack Indonesia (OS-ID) is an official OpenStack community (under Open Infrastructure Foundation) based in Indonesia. This community was established for all Indonesians who are interested in OpenStack projects/services.
In 2019, we held the first official community meetup in Jakarta and repeated monthly in several cities around Indonesia. First Indonesia Open Infrastructure Day was successfully held in November 2019 in Surabaya, and Last 2020 held the Open Infrastructure Day Indonesia event virtually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenStack Korea User Group</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/openstack-kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/openstack-kr/</guid>
      <description>OpenStack is cloud operating system which can manage massive computing in data center, storage, network resource and provisioning by APIs. As an official user group, OpenStack Korea Community actively engages with many OpenStack users and interested people through various communication channels such as Facebook, mailing list, IRC, and Slack (sign up), as well as various regular seminars, study activities, and translation team activities. OpenStack Korea Community held 1st OpenStack Day Korea event in 2014, and has held events every year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Canonical is the publisher of Ubuntu, the OS for most public cloud workloads as well as the emerging categories of smart gateways, self-driving cars, and advanced robots. Canonical provides enterprise security, support, and services to commercial users of Ubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu China Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-cn/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu China LoCo Team is an official local community in China approved by Ubuntu Community Council.
In 2005, the Ubuntu community in China started to form a team to take care of localization efforts of Ubuntu and the team soon transformed into an active community to promote Ubuntu and attract new comers. The Ubuntu China LoCo Team have so far organized over 100 local Ubuntu events and even more joint events, with very wide cooperation with academic institutions and commercial companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Hong Kong Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-hk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-hk/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu LoCo Hong Kong Team is a group of volunteers come together to share, enjoy, advocate and promote the usage of Ubuntu Linux in Hong Kong. The team will help to raise a local community and help others resolving difficulties when using Ubuntu Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Japanese Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-jp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-jp/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Japanese Team is voluntary group that intent improving and expanding Ubuntu in Japan, and is verified as an official Ubuntu LoCo till 2005.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Korea Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-kr/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Korea Community is an official verified LoCo(Local Community) Team by Ubuntu Community Council in South Korea.
The Ubuntu Korean community started in 2005, very small. But it&amp;rsquo;s now one of the most active Open Source communities in South Korea. We are continuing to carry out activities that can be helpful to Ubuntu users in Korea and broadly to people related to IT in Korea.
We hold various seminars, conferences, community-driven projects, joint seminars with other communities, and contribution workshops every year, and we also exchange with various overseas open source communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Kylin</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-kylin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-kylin/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Kylin is an official flavor of Ubuntu. It committed to bringing an easy, excellent, expert, and elaborate Linux distribution to users worldwide. It integrates the independently developed UKUI desktop environment which adheres to the friendly and simple design, aka Ubuntu Kylin User Interface. It includes more than 20 applications developed for ordinary users to enjoy a pleasant life and easy office operating system experience.  Links to social media</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Malaysia Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-my/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-my/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Malaysia Local Community Started on July 2005, the Malaysian Team has been approved as official LoCo Team since 2009 and we have already grown to over 200 members. We aim to provide free community support to users of any of the Ubuntu flavours as well as advocating the use of Ubuntu to individuals and organizations a like.
The LoCo is meant for anyone residing in Malaysia who uses or is interested in Ubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Myanmar Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-mm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-mm/</guid>
      <description>Note: Due to this local community&amp;rsquo;s country level situation, Ubuntu Myanmar Community is volunteering only when they have some chance to participate.
 We, Ubuntu Myanmar Loco team is an Ubuntu Council-recognized Loco Team that is offering support in the ease use of Ubuntu Operating System in computers across Myanmar.
Ubuntu for Myanmar initiated action in 2009. It was a youth organization that had been continuously organizing Ubuntu and Ubuntu-related Open Source software events, free workshops and had been an active organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Taiwan Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-tw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-tw/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Taiwan LoCo Team a.k.a Ubuntu-TW is a group of volunteers who enjoy Ubuntu and love to share, promote and make helps in Taiwan since 2005.
Our aim is make Ubuntu more easily to get start and more friendly to use for Traditional Chinese users.
We involving in localization, making workshop and collaborate with other FLOSS/Open-culture Communities like Mozilla Taiwan Community(MozTW), Open Culture Foundation(OCF), Linux user groups in Taiwan, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Unity Remix</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-unity-remix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-unity-remix/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Unity Remix is an Ubuntu remix (unofficial flavour) which uses Unity7 instead of gnome-shell. The latest stable release of Ubuntu Unity is 21.04 and we are also working on the desktop successor of Unity7, UnityX.
 Web: https://ubuntuunity.org Twitter: https://twitter.com/ubuntu_unity Telegram: https://t.me/ubuntuunityannouncements Discord: https://discord.gg/M2AWuCK GitLab: https://gitlab.com/ubuntu-unity  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UbuntuDDE Remix</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-dde-remix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-dde-remix/</guid>
      <description>UbuntuDDE Remix is a GNU/Linux distribution based on Ubuntu with the most beautiful desktop environment. It is a Remix flavor of Ubuntu desktop with Deepin Desktop Environment (DDE). The initial release was 20.04 (focal) as the project got started during the first wave of Covid 19. It is not yet an official flavor recognized by Canonical Ltd. but the release schedule is aligned closely with the other Ubuntu flavors. The latest release of the UbuntuDDE Remix is 21.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhaTap Labs</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/whatap-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/whatap-labs/</guid>
      <description>WhaTap Labs provides IT monitoring service &amp;ldquo;WhaTap&amp;rdquo;. We make IT services easier and more reliable for developers and operators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WSLHUB (WSL Korea User Group)</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/wslhub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/wslhub/</guid>
      <description> WSLHUB is a local user group community in South Korea. Our community members are especially interested in WSL and the Linux Ecosystem. Our community currently runs several open-source projects(such as WslManager, WslQuery) and a Facebook group to communicate with our members.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
