<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ubucon Asia 2021</title>
    <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ubucon Asia 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 01:49:00 +0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://2021.ubucon.asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cloudmate joins as our Silver sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-08-10-cloudmate-joins-as-silver-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 01:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-08-10-cloudmate-joins-as-silver-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We are gladly to announce Cloudmate as our part of Silver Sponsor.
Cloudmate is an certified CSP(Cloud Service Provider) company in Seoul, South Korea. They provides professional managed service on cloud environment. Based on experiences from MNCs, Cloudmate has its best certified engineers and developers in the cloud sector. Through the professional managed service, Cloudmate supports systematic management and its cloud infrastructure to the customers. Furthermore, Cloudmate also offers consulting for cloud service to industries that are adapting cloud infrastructure for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello UbuCon Asia speakers!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-30-speaker-schedules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 12:47:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-30-speaker-schedules/</guid>
      <description>Hello UbuCon Asia 2021 speakers! Thanks again for submitting your proposals for the first UbuCon Asia! We just completed reviewing proposals and now reaching out each person to confirm speaker participation.
Confirm your participation If your proposal was accepted, We&amp;rsquo;ll send you an email to confirm whether you&amp;rsquo;ll give speech on the event. You may also check eventyay to see whether your proposal was accepted. To confirm your speaker participation, simply reply us and tell us you will participate as speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you to Ubuntu for Join as Diamond Sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-24-ubuntu-joins-as-diamond-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 01:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-24-ubuntu-joins-as-diamond-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We are gladly to announce Ubuntu as our part of Diamond Sponsor.
The Ubuntu desktop as we know is the world&amp;rsquo;s most widely used Linux workstation platform, powering the work of engineers across the globe. Ubuntu today has many flavours and dozens of specialized derivatives. All share common infrastructure and software, making Ubuntu a unique single platform that scales from consumer electronics to the desktop and up into the cloud for enterprise computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for speakers is now closed!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-15-cfs-is-now-closed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:22:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-15-cfs-is-now-closed/</guid>
      <description>Hello folks! Calling for speakers is now closed!
Thanks to everyone who submitted session proposals to the first Ubuntu conference in Asia! We have received total 46 proposals! This includes&amp;hellip;
 Talks &amp;amp; Extended Talks Lightning talks Workshops Panel discussions  But this does not includes social events and sponsor sessions yet. In next 2 weeks, Our content team will review your submissions until the end of this month. Content team folks may contact to each person who submitted proposals to ask some further details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double check your proposal submissions before deadline</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-11-double-check-proposal-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 15:34:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-11-double-check-proposal-submission/</guid>
      <description>Call for speakers will close soon on July 14th 23:59 UTC+9! If you have submitted any session proposals, please double check your submissions and update it if required before the deadline comes.
Your speaker info Please see the image and description below and check your speaker info submissions once again to see if anything missing.
 Name: Your full name (e.g. Youngbin Han) Email: Your email contact address. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive proposal review result with the email address you entered here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for proposals extended by July 14</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-30-cfp-extended-by-july-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 08:31:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-30-cfp-extended-by-july-14/</guid>
      <description>If you have been rush into submitting proposal, You now have extra 2 more weeks to finalize submitting your proposlas! UbuCon Asia 2021 Calling for proposal due date has been extended by July 14th 23:59 (UTC+9).
For your informations, See details you need know from below before submitting proposals. Please do not hesitate to contact Ubucon Asia team whether through social media or email if you are not sure about writing your proposal or preparing your presentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become our individual patron today</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-24-donation-ticket/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:20:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-24-donation-ticket/</guid>
      <description>To raise enough amount of money required stably, We&amp;rsquo;re announcing another way to contribute on our event. From today, You can contribute to our successful event by becoming one of our individual patrons!
To become our patron, Visit our event page on eventyay.com and follow steps below.
 Sign in with your eventyay.com account. Scroll down to &amp;ldquo;Tickets&amp;rdquo; section, You will see &amp;ldquo;Sign Up to Join Ubucon Asia 2021&amp;rdquo; which is free ticket and &amp;ldquo;Donation Ticket&amp;rdquo; Set price of donation ticket you would like to donate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Proposals</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-30-calling-for-proposals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:39:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-30-calling-for-proposals/</guid>
      <description>UbuCon Asia 2021 team have been calling for speakers, volunteers, sponsors and community partners from earlier this month. As this is the first time to organize UbuCon Asia, Our proposal period is relatively longer then other conferences. This is a reminder post that includes all details for each items and URL link to them.
Calling for speakers  Submit until June 30th 2021, Session acceptance will be on July 30th 2021 Session type: Talk(30min, 45min), Lightning talk(5min), Workshop(1hour, 2hour), Panel duscussions(55mins) All session duration includes time for question and answer For &amp;ldquo;Talk&amp;rdquo; type session, you can submit pre-recorded session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Video Translation Volunteers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-calling-for-translation-volunteers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 12:01:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-calling-for-translation-volunteers/</guid>
      <description>As we begin calling for speakers, We&amp;rsquo;re now also calling for translation volunteers from today. Translation volunteers will colloborate local community to translate pre-recorded sessions from following languages to English.
 Korean - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Korea Community Japanese - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Japanese Community Chinese(China) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu China Community Chinese(Taiwan) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Taiwan Community Cantonese(Hong Kong) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Hong Kong Community Indonesian - You will collaborate GNOME Indonesia and Openstack Indonesia  We will use speech-to-text and machine translation tool to automate subtitle works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Speakers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-call-for-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 09:50:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-call-for-speakers/</guid>
      <description>The first Ubuntu Conference in Asia (Ubucon Asia 2021) is four months ahead! Ubucon Asia 2021 Call for Speakers is now open until 30 June, and talks acceptance will be on 30 July.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the reference topics for you to discuss in Ubucon Asia 2021:
 Desktop Server/Infrastructure/Cloud Windows Subsystem for Linux(WSL) Localization(L10n)/Fonts/Input Methods Internet of Things(IoT)/Embedded Security Community/Social Context Case Studies etc.  We have some sessions to talk with two days event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubucon Asia 2021 Plan updates</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-04-21-some-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:10:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-04-21-some-updates/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been about 3 months after I published post &amp;ldquo;Looking for organizers&amp;rdquo;. Last 3 months, many Ubuntu Local communities and other FLOSS communities contact me to join Ubucon Asia 2021 team. Today, We have 12 host communities from 10 different regions in the team. Some organizers from those communities with excellent experience with organizing international events also joined our team.
And with this Ubucon Asia 2021 team, We&amp;rsquo;ve been made many progress until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>*No sessions yet</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/no-sessions-yet/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jan 2021 10:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/no-sessions-yet/</guid>
      <description>We don&amp;rsquo;t have any scheduled sessions and schedules for calling for papers yet. Notice for CFPs and session informations will be updated later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for organizers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 01:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers/</guid>
      <description>In Asia, You can find various community conferences about open source and linux that covers Asia region. Good examples of this are:
 openSUSE.Asia GNOME.Asia LibreOffice Asia Conference PyCon APAC FOSSASIA Summit and more&amp;hellip;  For past a few years, when I was the leader of Ubuntu Korea Community, I attended several conferences overseas to not just meet and learn but also to interact with Ubuntu local communities overseas. Especially, communities located near South Korea region.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>.NET DEV</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/dotnetdevkr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/dotnetdevkr/</guid>
      <description> .Net Dev is a local .Net user group in South Korea. Our community members are especially interested in .NET development and its ecosystem.  Including ASP.NET, EF, Blazor, etc&amp;hellip;   We runs regular local conference called &amp;ldquo;.NET Conf x Seoul&amp;rdquo; every year and &amp;ldquo;.NET Conf Mini&amp;rdquo; almost every quarter. .NET Conf Korea by .NET Dev: https://dotnetconf.kr .NET Medium Blog: https://blog.dotnetdev.kr .NET Dev Discourse: https://forum.dotnetdev.kr  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Ubucon Asia 2021</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/about/</guid>
      <description>Welcome, and thank you for your interest on Ubucon Asia.
Ubucon Asia is an event organized by Ubuntu Communities in Asia. It&amp;rsquo;s for everyone who involved with or interested in Ubuntu, Linux and other Free and Open source technologies. Ubucon Asia is also a place for Ubuntu people from Asia to connect, learn, and share their knowlegdes each other.
Ubucon Asia 2021, the first Ubuntu conference in Asia will be a virtual conference driven by multiple Ubuntu LoCos from Asia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a sponsor</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your interest in Ubuntu and Ubucon Asia.
As a non-profit and community organized event, Even Ubucon Asia 2021 is fully virtual event, We still need support from sponsors to make the event happen.
By becoming one of our sponsors, you are directly contributing to research and development of Ubuntu and Open Source Software, and also making Open Source Community more active and sustainable.
Your contribution makes it possible for us to bring a large number of Ubuntu users and contributors across Asia to connect, interact, help and learn together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudmate</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/cloudmate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/cloudmate/</guid>
      <description>Cloudmate is the certified CSP company that located in Seoul, Korea.
Cloudmate provides professional managed service on cloud environment. Based on experiences from MNCs, Cloudmate has its best certified engineers and developers in the cloud sector. Through the professional managed service, Cloudmate supports systematic management and its cloud infrastructure to the customers. Furthermore, Cloudmate also offers consulting for cloud service to industries that are adapting cloud infrastructure for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debian Malaysia</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/debian-malaysia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/debian-malaysia/</guid>
      <description>Malaysian Debian GNU/Linux enthusiasts community
You can be reach us by various means:
 Chat: Telegram group (https://t.me/debianmalaysia) / IRC #debian-malaysia on Freenode / Matrix /join #freenode_#debian-malaysia:matrix.org Website: http://debianmalaysia.gitlab.io (mirror: https://malaysia-team.pages.debian.net) Mailing lists: Debmal google group (https://groups.google.com/g/debmal) Social media: Twitter - https://twitter.com/debianmalaysia / Mastodon - https://linuxrocks.online/@debianmalaysia (both cross-posted)  Please choose what ever communication channel and you are welcome!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSS Nepal Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/foss-np/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/foss-np/</guid>
      <description>FOSS Nepal Community is a team of volunteers who believe in the usage of Free/Open Source Software (FOSS). The primary objective of the community is to promote, develop and diversify the usage of Free/Open Source Software in Nepal.
 To raise awareness among general public, government bodies, private sector, civil society, educational institutions and media for expanding the scope of Information and Communication Technology (ICT) via Free and Open Source Software To sensitize general public, government bodies, civil society and media for the implementation of e-governance by means of FOSS; the optimal solution for e-governance Advocacy for alternatives in Intellectual Property Rights (IPR) specific to ICT To enhance the capacity of IT professionals by promoting inclusion of Free and Open Source Software in educational system and providing platform for IT professionals to make them globally saleable.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FOSSASIA</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/fossasia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/fossasia/</guid>
      <description>FOSSASIA develops Open Source software and hardware solutions with a global developer community from its base in Asia and organizes Open Technology events around the year. The organization also runs coding programs and development contests.
The annual FOSSASIA Summit is the premier Open Technology event in Asia for developers, start-ups, and contributors. It is a unique opportunity to share knowledge and experience about Open Source and meet interesting contributors.
FOSSASIA was founded in 2009 by Mario Behling and Hong Phuc Dang.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gimpscape ID</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/gimpscape-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/gimpscape-id/</guid>
      <description>Gimpscape ID community is a one of design community from Indonesia that has oriented to the use of Free/Open Source Software (FOSS). On various occasions, Gimpscape ID always strives to contribute to activities related to free/open source software.
 Telegram https://t.me/gimpscape Instagram https://instagram/gimpscape_id  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/gnome-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/gnome-id/</guid>
      <description>GNOME Indonesia (GNOME-ID) is a non-profit community founded to support the use, promotion and assistance of users of the GNOME desktop environment in Indonesia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join as Partner Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/join-as-partner-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/join-as-partner-community/</guid>
      <description>To promote UbuCon Asia event across Asia much further, We’re looking for partner communities. By becoming our partner community, Your community will collaborate with UbuCon Asia team to cross-promote each other’s community and event. This will be a big help for both partner communities and UbuCon Asia to connect with even more diverse people and encourage them to participate and engage.
To learn more about our partner community program, please refer to our brochure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KLAS (Kelompok Linux Arek Suroboyo)</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/klas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/klas/</guid>
      <description>Arek Suroboyo Linux Group (Surabaya Linux User Group) (KLAS) is one of the Linux user groups in the city of Surabaya. We have been around since 1995, and are still active today. We have several routine agendas and facilities that we do and until now we have facilitated them to support Go FOSS activities in Surabaya, such as:
 Cangkrukan KLAS Local Conferences (Open Infrastucture Day 2019) International Conferences (openSUSE.Asia Summit 2019, GNOME.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/microsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/microsoft/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenStack Indonesia Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/openstack-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/openstack-id/</guid>
      <description>OpenStack Indonesia (OS-ID) is an official OpenStack community (under Open Infrastructure Foundation) based in Indonesia. This community was established for all Indonesians who are interested in OpenStack projects/services.
In 2019, we held the first official community meetup in Jakarta and repeated monthly in several cities around Indonesia. First Indonesia Open Infrastructure Day was successfully held in November 2019 in Surabaya, and Last 2020 held the Open Infrastructure Day Indonesia event virtually.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenStack Korea User Group</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/openstack-kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/openstack-kr/</guid>
      <description>OpenStack is cloud operating system which can manage massive computing in data center, storage, network resource and provisioning by APIs. As an official user group, OpenStack Korea Community actively engages with many OpenStack users and interested people through various communication channels such as Facebook, mailing list, IRC, and Slack (sign up), as well as various regular seminars, study activities, and translation team activities. OpenStack Korea Community held 1st OpenStack Day Korea event in 2014, and has held events every year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>Canonical is the publisher of Ubuntu, the OS for most public cloud workloads as well as the emerging categories of smart gateways, self-driving cars, and advanced robots. Canonical provides enterprise security, support, and services to commercial users of Ubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu China Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-cn/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu China LoCo Team is an official local community in China approved by Ubuntu Community Council.
In 2005, the Ubuntu community in China started to form a team to take care of localization efforts of Ubuntu and the team soon transformed into an active community to promote Ubuntu and attract new comers. The Ubuntu China LoCo Team have so far organized over 100 local Ubuntu events and even more joint events, with very wide cooperation with academic institutions and commercial companies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Hong Kong Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-hk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-hk/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu LoCo Hong Kong Team is a group of volunteers come together to share, enjoy, advocate and promote the usage of Ubuntu Linux in Hong Kong. The team will help to raise a local community and help others resolving difficulties when using Ubuntu Linux.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Japanese Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-jp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-jp/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Japanese Team is voluntary group that intent improving and expanding Ubuntu in Japan, and is verified as an official Ubuntu LoCo till 2005.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Korea Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-kr/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Korea Community is an official verified LoCo(Local Community) Team by Ubuntu Community Council in South Korea.
The Ubuntu Korean community started in 2005, very small. But it&amp;rsquo;s now one of the most active Open Source communities in South Korea. We are continuing to carry out activities that can be helpful to Ubuntu users in Korea and broadly to people related to IT in Korea.
We hold various seminars, conferences, community-driven projects, joint seminars with other communities, and contribution workshops every year, and we also exchange with various overseas open source communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Kylin</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-kylin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-kylin/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Kylin is an official flavor of Ubuntu. It committed to bringing an easy, excellent, expert, and elaborate Linux distribution to users worldwide. It integrates the independently developed UKUI desktop environment which adheres to the friendly and simple design, aka Ubuntu Kylin User Interface. It includes more than 20 applications developed for ordinary users to enjoy a pleasant life and easy office operating system experience.  Links to social media</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Malaysia Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-my/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-my/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Malaysia Local Community Started on July 2005, the Malaysian Team has been approved as official LoCo Team since 2009 and we have already grown to over 200 members. We aim to provide free community support to users of any of the Ubuntu flavours as well as advocating the use of Ubuntu to individuals and organizations a like.
The LoCo is meant for anyone residing in Malaysia who uses or is interested in Ubuntu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Myanmar Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-mm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-mm/</guid>
      <description>Note: Due to this local community&amp;rsquo;s country level situation, Ubuntu Myanmar Community is volunteering only when they have some chance to participate.
 We, Ubuntu Myanmar Loco team is an Ubuntu Council-recognized Loco Team that is offering support in the ease use of Ubuntu Operating System in computers across Myanmar.
Ubuntu for Myanmar initiated action in 2009. It was a youth organization that had been continuously organizing Ubuntu and Ubuntu-related Open Source software events, free workshops and had been an active organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Taiwan Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-tw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-tw/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Taiwan LoCo Team a.k.a Ubuntu-TW is a group of volunteers who enjoy Ubuntu and love to share, promote and make helps in Taiwan since 2005.
Our aim is make Ubuntu more easily to get start and more friendly to use for Traditional Chinese users.
We involving in localization, making workshop and collaborate with other FLOSS/Open-culture Communities like Mozilla Taiwan Community(MozTW), Open Culture Foundation(OCF), Linux user groups in Taiwan, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Unity Remix</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-unity-remix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-unity-remix/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Unity Remix is an Ubuntu remix (unofficial flavour) which uses Unity7 instead of gnome-shell. The latest stable release of Ubuntu Unity is 21.04 and we are also working on the desktop successor of Unity7, UnityX.
 Web: https://ubuntuunity.org Twitter: https://twitter.com/ubuntu_unity Telegram: https://t.me/ubuntuunityannouncements Discord: https://discord.gg/M2AWuCK GitLab: https://gitlab.com/ubuntu-unity  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>UbuntuDDE Remix</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-dde-remix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-dde-remix/</guid>
      <description>UbuntuDDE Remix is a GNU/Linux distribution based on Ubuntu with the most beautiful desktop environment. It is a Remix flavor of Ubuntu desktop with Deepin Desktop Environment (DDE). The initial release was 20.04 (focal) as the project got started during the first wave of Covid 19. It is not yet an official flavor recognized by Canonical Ltd. but the release schedule is aligned closely with the other Ubuntu flavors. The latest release of the UbuntuDDE Remix is 21.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WhaTap Labs</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/whatap-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/whatap-labs/</guid>
      <description>WhaTap Labs provides IT monitoring service &amp;ldquo;WhaTap&amp;rdquo;. We make IT services easier and more reliable for developers and operators.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WSLHUB (WSL Korea User Group)</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/wslhub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/wslhub/</guid>
      <description> WSLHUB is a local user group community in South Korea. Our community members are especially interested in WSL and the Linux Ecosystem. Our community currently runs several open-source projects(such as WslManager, WslQuery) and a Facebook group to communicate with our members.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
