<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ubucon Asia 2021</title>
    <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ubucon Asia 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 23:30:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://2021.ubucon.asia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UbuCon Asia 2021 Final report</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-12-01-ubucon-asia-2021-final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 23:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-12-01-ubucon-asia-2021-final-report/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been about a year since we started to gather organizers, form a team. And last September, with a lot of support from Ubuntu Community and other many Free and Open Source Communities around Asia, We successfully organized the first UbuCon Asia which was a virtual event.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this report, We would like to wrap-up and finalize our event activities for this year. Then we would like to think about how we can do better at the next UbuCon Asia. We hope this report would be helpful for other Ubuntu community folks who would like to organize similar events.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swag updates</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-10-20-swag-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-10-20-swag-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Swags - Zipup hoodie, T-Shirt and Stickers!&#34; src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-10-20-swag-updates/swags.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;free-swags-updates&#34;&gt;Free swags updates&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re currently distributing swags of UbuCon Asia 2021! For Organizers, Speakers, Patrons and Volunteers, We already distributed E-Gift cards via email that can be redeemed on out Swag shop. Swags for Sponsors (5 Qty for each) and Attendees (One for each) who won for swag lottery or found treasure during treasure hunt will be also distributed soon. It will take about 1~2 weeks to proceed with purchasing E-Gift cards and distributing via email.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubucon Asia 2021 - YouTube Premiere Restream - 9-10 Oct, 2021</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-10-05-restream-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-10-05-restream-schedule/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you once again to everyone who took part in the first Ubucon Asia 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much to our speakers, who spent a great deal of time preparing their wonderful presentations. For anyone who missed any of them, or would like to watch them again, we are announcing that they will be restreamed on YouTube on 9-10 Oct 2021 and will thereafter be available to watch on demand. Details are below.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Closing session 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/closing_session/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:50:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/closing_session/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;rsquo;s wrap up this year&amp;rsquo;s 2 days the first UbuCon Asia event! And see you on next year!(Maybe in-person?)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNOME.Asia Summit 2021 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/gnomeasia_summit_2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/gnomeasia_summit_2021/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GNOME.Asia Summit 2021 hosted by Malaysia people will be on upcoming November! Learn some details about the event on this short session!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Organize Virtual Event with Open Source Tools 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/organize_virtual_event_with_open_source_tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 19:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/organize_virtual_event_with_open_source_tools/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This talk aims to enable community organizers to organize event with open source tools focusing on Eventyay and open source video solutions.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing Integration Test with WSL APIs 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/developing_integration_test_with_wsl_apis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 18:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/developing_integration_test_with_wsl_apis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This session delivers how you can develop your own integration-test environment build tool with the WSL SDK project. WSL SDK project is an open-source project that provides versatile and robust WSL management APIs without any restrictions.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Also, I will share how I overcame technical hurdles with this project. If you are interested in the Win32 native programming aspect, you may obtain some insights from my talk.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Annual Microsoft MVP Award since 2009&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;WSLHUB, .NET DEV Community Staff&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;DEVSISTERS DevOps Engineer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Getting Closer with Kelompok Linux Arek Suroboyo and Buaya Linux Repository Server 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/getting_closer_with_kelompok_linux_arek_suroboyo_and_buaya_linux_repository_server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/getting_closer_with_kelompok_linux_arek_suroboyo_and_buaya_linux_repository_server/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Kelompok Linux Arek Suroboyo is a community of Linux users based in Surabaya. This community was formed in 1995 by a group of information technology activists in Surabaya. Because of concern for open source software products in Surabaya. In its development, many ups and downs occurred in the community camp as well as on the way to introducing the city of Surabaya to information and communication technology in the field of open-source software. Many conferences have been passed by Kelompok Linux Arek Suroboyo. As organizers, committees, partner communities, and as participants. Among them is the openSUSE Asia Summit2019 as a community partner, committee, as well as a speaker. In addition, the LibreOfficeConference was held in Taipei in 2019. Kelompok Linux Arek Suroboyo is an OSS community that already has a network and reach in Indonesia and the world. In Ubuntu Conference Asia 2021,the Community will be present as Community Partners and will share their experiences of ups and downs in managing this large community and the achievements that have been achieved.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Having fun with Flutter Desktop development 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/having_fun_with_flutter_desktop_development/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 18:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/having_fun_with_flutter_desktop_development/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Google and Canonical annouced Flutter support for Linux recently but have you wondered what exactly is Flutter? Why is it everywhere lately? Where can it run and is it easy to write apps in it? If you want to know more what is possible with Flutter and how it differs from other UI frameworks, join this session.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/having_fun_with_flutter_desktop_development/having_fun_with_flutter_desktop_development_script.pdf&#34;&gt;Get Transcription&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am programming Flutter from its early stages. Active member of London Flutter Community. Passionate about reactive programming and open source. Linux and open source fan. Mechanical keyboards enthusiast.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OEM metapackages &amp; Concourse CI 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/oem_metapackages__concourse_ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/oem_metapackages__concourse_ci/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;What are OEM metapackages?What is Concourse CI?How to use Concourse CI on OEM metapackages?&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Debian Developer / Ubuntu Contributing Developer / GNOME Emeritus Member / Canonical Employee&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://hackmd.io/@fourdollars/oem-metapackages-and-concourse-ci#/&#34;&gt;See slide on hackmd.io&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;iframe src=&#34;https://hackmd.io/@fourdollars/oem-metapackages-and-concourse-ci#/&#34; width=&#34;576&#34; height=&#34;420&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; webkitallowfullscreen mozallowfullscreen allowfullscreen&gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Private Lab Virtualization Using Multipass and Deploy Apps web-based on Ubuntu Server. 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/private_lab_virtualization_using_multipass_and_deploy_apps_web_based_on_ubuntu_server/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/private_lab_virtualization_using_multipass_and_deploy_apps_web_based_on_ubuntu_server/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;introduction&#34;&gt;Introduction:&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Multipass is a virtualization product from Ubuntu that we can use to create a virtual machine and support cloud-init like in a public cloud. Multipass can be run in a local environment for free and is very suitable for development.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;here-are-some-discussion-points&#34;&gt;Here are some discussion points:&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Reasons to use Multipass&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Advantages and Disadvantages of Multipass&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to install Multipass&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to use Multipass and basic commands in Multipass&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Basic Cloud-init&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Install web-based applications demonstration on VMs Multipass&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Additional material on Multipass integration&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/private_lab_virtualization_using_multipass_and_deploy_apps_web_based_on_ubuntu_server/Multipass.pptx&#34;&gt;Get Slide(*.pptx)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The challenge of Using LibreOffice &amp; Building Local Community in Korea 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/the_challenge_of_using_libreoffice__building_local_community_in_korea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/the_challenge_of_using_libreoffice__building_local_community_in_korea/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In South Korea, Both HWPML(file format: hwp) and ODF are a Document format standard as a public sector. The Republic of Korea government adopted OpenDocument as a part of Korean Industrial Standards KS X ISO/IEC 26300 in 2007.However, In South Korea&amp;rsquo;s academic field, the public &amp;amp; private sector, It is still using HWP as a document standard. They are still made and distributed in .hwp format. I&amp;rsquo;m a Full-time worker(Developer) &amp;amp; University student in Korea. This year, I transferred to Korea National Open University, major in Chinese Language &amp;amp; Literature &amp;amp; University student in Korea. As a university student, I talk about the inconvenience of using ODF when making documents in Korea. Also, I introduce the activities of the LibreOffice community since 2020 in Korea. Last year(2020) and this year(2021) activities, such as participating in NIPA(The National IT Industry Promotion Agency - IT industry promotion organization operated by the Republic of Korea Government)&amp;rsquo;s open source activity hold programs, supporting  Korea-Japan LibreOffice conference by NIPA, and LibreOffice Local Community&amp;rsquo;s activities (such as Hacktoberfest activities).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Mengetik Aksara Pegon dengan Ubuntu 20.04.2 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/mengetik_aksara_pegon_dengan_ubuntu_20042/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:10:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/mengetik_aksara_pegon_dengan_ubuntu_20042/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Menurut wikipedia, Pegon is an Arabic script used to write the Javanese, Madurese and Sundanese languages, as an alternative to the Latin script or the Javanese script.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pada Ubuntu 20.04.2 belum tersedia Keyboard Pegon. Pegon merupakan penulisan abjad Jawa atau Sunda atau Indonesia menggunakan abjad Arab. Oleh karena itu sebagian besar karakter Pegon sudah tersedia pada blok Unicode Arab.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Di MTs Irsyaduth Thullab, soal cbt mata pelajaran kitab kuning ditulis dengan aksara Pegon walau dengan berbagai kendala seperti;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>If you need LAMP Stack, Journey to Ubuntu with WSL2 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/if_you_need_lamp_stack_journey_to_ubuntu_with_wsl2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:05:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/if_you_need_lamp_stack_journey_to_ubuntu_with_wsl2/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I needed LAMP Stack for working with Wordpress.&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m not a developer or software engineer. and I just had only one small laptop.&#xA;I couldn&amp;rsquo;t use public cloud for security.&#xA;So, I fell in love with WSL2.&#xA;At first, I was a little hard to set. but, It was not so hard to drive.&#xA;Let me show you, how I started setting ubuntu with WSL2 For beginers.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Life is just TEST. YALA and Industrial Engineering. Love panda bear and Mullae-dong, Seoul.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>openEuler社区的开源合规实践(Open source compliance practice of the openEuler community) 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/openeuleropen_source_compliance_practice_of_the_openeuler_community/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 17:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/openeuleropen_source_compliance_practice_of_the_openeuler_community/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;openEuler通过社区合作，打造创新平台，构建支持多处理架构、统一和开放的操作系统，推动软硬件应用生态繁荣发展。&#xA;openEuler is an innovative platform nurtured by community collaboration. It aims to build a unified and open OS that supports multiple processor architectures, and to advance the hardware/software application ecosystem.&#xA;openEuler社区在开源合规方面还不是很成熟，但已经努力摸索出一条有自己特色的发展之路，希望借助UbuCon Asia 2021这个平台与更多的开源伙伴交流促进。&#xA;OpenEuler community is not very mature in terms of open source compliance, but it has worked hard to find a development path with its own characteristics, hoping to use the platform of UbuCon Asia 2021 to communicate with more open source partners.&#xA;我将对openEuler社区的开源合规实践作一个简单的分享。&#xA;I&amp;rsquo;m going to share the open source compliance practices of the openeuler community.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Using kexec to speed-up reboot 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/using_kexec_to_speed_up_reboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 16:55:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/using_kexec_to_speed_up_reboot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;kexec loads a new kernel image without going through the hardware&amp;rsquo;s initialization stage, drastically speeding up the reboot process.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this lightning talk, pros and cons of kexec will be listed along with how-to instructions on using kexec on Ubuntu 20.04.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re currently using kexec to speed up our development and successfully reduced the reboot time from 2 minutes to 10 seconds on a server machine.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m a 23 years old student at DGIST DataLab, currently pursuing a Ph.D in Information &amp;amp; Communication Engineering.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Introduction Indonesia Communities 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/introduction_indonesia_communities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 16:50:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/introduction_indonesia_communities/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Introduction to Indonesia Communities&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu on Cloud Environments 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/ubuntu_on_cloud_environments/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 16:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/ubuntu_on_cloud_environments/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sponsored session (Cloudmate Co. Ltd.)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this session, we will discuss about how Ubuntu and other Linux are compatible to major Public Cloud Providers such as AWS, Azure, and GCP. We will also talk about what kind of images, services, subscriptions, and products are available from them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;sejun-kim&#34;&gt;Sejun Kim&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Orgenizer of &amp;ldquo;The AzureLife(애저로운 생활)&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft Azure MVP&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cloud Architect&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cloudmate Technical Enginnering Leader.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;junhyeon-bae&#34;&gt;Junhyeon Bae&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Manager of Lead Engineering Team at Cloudmate Co. Ltd.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Microsoft MVP (Azure)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Organizer, Ubuntu Korea Community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Community Advisor, 코딩이랑 무관합니다만,(Well it&amp;rsquo;s nothing to do with coding)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Web Hosting Server using Ubuntu and Cyberpanel 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/web_hosting_server_using_ubuntu_and_cyberpanel/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 15:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/web_hosting_server_using_ubuntu_and_cyberpanel/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this material I will discuss cyberpanel on the ubuntu server that I use for daily web hosting at my office.CyberPanel is a web control panel that is directly supported by OpenLiteSpeed, with a number of other excellent features such as GIT Manager, Docker Manager, SSL, and others.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Experienced System Administrator with a demonstrated history of working in the internet industry. Skilled in Network Administration, Server Administration, Computer Network Operations, Open Source Software, and Computer Repair.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>K8s - MicroK8s &amp; K3s 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/k8s___microk8s__k3s/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 15:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/k8s___microk8s__k3s/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;microk8s&#34;&gt;MicroK8s&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;High availability K8s&#xA;Low-ops, minimal production Kubernetes,&#xA;for devs, cloud, clusters, workstations, Edge and IoT.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://microk8s.io/&#34;&gt;https://microk8s.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;k3s&#34;&gt;K3s&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lightweight Kubernetes&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://k3s.io/&#34;&gt;https://k3s.io/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I have played around with Linux since 2004, from Web Designer to Web Administrator (For LAMP) with Ubuntu being my main choice. I settled on Ubuntu as my favourite Linux distro. I will Promote About Linux and Ubuntu Distro since 2009., Raspberry Pi since 2013, Container LXD at 2014, Open Stack at 2016, DevOps at 2018, Docker and Kubernetes at 2019.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu OS &amp; Service patch management using Ansible 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/ubuntu_os__service_patch_management_using_ansible/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 15:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/ubuntu_os__service_patch_management_using_ansible/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To patch just one system, the administrator must identify that a patch is available, download it, and then deploy it to the system. In an enterprise environment, there could be hundreds of servers to manage, so the job of patch management becomes an all-day responsibility with the added risk of reboot fails after installation. Instead of manual updates, administrators can free up time and organize patches using automation tools.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Using Ansible made patch management simpler than ever. Ansible provides solutions for Ubuntu patch management which helps admins ensure that all the Ubuntu machines on the network are up to date with critical/recent Ubuntu security patches that are released and there are no security vulnerabilities in the network. You can automate the complete process and ensure that all your systems and service required are up-to-date.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Automating boring and repetitive UbuCon Asia video and subtitle stuffs 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/automating_boring_and_repetitive_ubucon_asia_video_and_subtitle_stuffs/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 14:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/automating_boring_and_repetitive_ubucon_asia_video_and_subtitle_stuffs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Whether it&amp;rsquo;s online or offline event, There&amp;rsquo;s always boring and repetitive jobs for event organizers and volunteers. Putting cover on session videos and making subtitle for videos are part of them.&#xA;UbuCon Asia team, is no exception. But like you and other ordinary people, our organizers also have their own job and busy with that usually. As it&amp;rsquo;s first event we don&amp;rsquo;t even know if we can gather enough volunteers or gain sponsorship to hire some workers.&#xA;So, We decided to use some automation tools like CI/CD, Speech to text, Translation API, Video cover rendering template and so on to automate these boring job as much as possible and reduce cost at the same time.&#xA;In this session, I would like to share how we did this and what we&amp;rsquo;ve learned while trying to automate stuffs.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Judge A Book by Its Cover: Contributing to Open Source Communities with Graphic Design 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/dont_judge_a_book_by_its_cover_contributing_to_open_source_communities_with_graphic_design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 14:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/dont_judge_a_book_by_its_cover_contributing_to_open_source_communities_with_graphic_design/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this digital era, everyone uses multimedia in their daily life. Cell phones, social media, and the internet seem to be the new basic needs. Moreover, the pandemic has increased the intensity of gadget use due to limited mobility and physical activity. Like it or not, all activities turn to online activities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This makes business people, event organizers, and content creators compete for attention by displaying visuals and attractive appearances for each of their content. The open source community is among those who should be scrambling for attention. Therefore, graphic design is becoming increasingly important and needed so that the open source community does not lose its support, and remains attractive to new contributors.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Promote Ubuntu localization of the ethnic minorities in China
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/promote_ubuntu_localization_of_the_ethnic_groups_in_china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 13:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/promote_ubuntu_localization_of_the_ethnic_groups_in_china/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This talk is about how we process Chinese Tibetan localization in last year.  It includes the huge translation management, open source community and university collaboration, and the localization status of other ethnic groups in China.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Bugress Chang&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Snap in MicroOS 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/snap_in_microos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 13:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/snap_in_microos/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Snap in openSUSE MicroOS Desktop&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;According to openSUSE wiki, openSUSE MicroOS is an operating system you don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about. It&amp;rsquo;s designed for but not limited to container hosts and edge devices. openSUSE MicroOS Desktop is a MicroOS with a desktop-focused variant of MicroOS based on Tumbleweed. MicroOS Desktop is an immutable, rolling base as based on Tumbleweed.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Snaps are app packages for desktop, cloud, and IoT that are easy to install, secure, cross-platform, and dependency-free, developed by Canonical.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The input method, another way to edit Japenense documents, Hanjp project 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/the_input_method_another_way_to_edit_japenense_documents_hanjp_project/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 13:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/the_input_method_another_way_to_edit_japenense_documents_hanjp_project/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this session, I&amp;rsquo;d like to introduce about Hanjp Input Method project, first of all.&#xA;Its concept, the reasons why did I start the project, current state, and some demos are included.&#xA;Then, I will re-introduce it in techincal view.&#xA;Choosen languages and libraries, program structure, and project milestone are included.&#xA;Then lastly, I&amp;rsquo;d talk about community development.&#xA;Current contribution activity, Open Up activities(the open source activity) are included.&#xA;Please refer to URL below to get informed about Hanjp project&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ubuntu-kr/hanjp-im/tree/develop&#34;&gt;https://github.com/ubuntu-kr/hanjp-im/tree/develop&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UKUI3 Technology Sharing In Tablet Mode 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/ukui3_technology_sharing_in_tablet_mode/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Sep 2021 13:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/ukui3_technology_sharing_in_tablet_mode/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ukui 3.0 is a lightweight desktop environment based on Linux release developed by Kylin team. In addition to the traditional desktop mode, the tablet mode is also provided to meet the needs of various scenarios.We will share ukui&amp;rsquo;s experience and achievements in how to add support for tablet form and its future planning.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;R &amp;amp; D Manager of UbuntuKylin team&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Social event: Treasure Hunt! - Day 1 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/social_event___day_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 19:25:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/social_event___day_1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Treasure Hunt @ Gather Town!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Panel Discussion - Open Source Communities in Asia: Opportunities and Challenges  
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/panel_discussion___open_source_communities_in_asia_opportunities_and_challenges/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 18:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/panel_discussion___open_source_communities_in_asia_opportunities_and_challenges/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;We will hear from representatives of our hosts and open source communities in Asia. &lt;a href=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/&#34;&gt;https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Moderator: Hong Phuc Dang&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;slide: hello.pdf&#xA;speakers: TBC&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speakers&#34;&gt;About the speakers&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;hong-phuc-dang&#34;&gt;Hong Phuc Dang&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hong Phuc is the founder of FOSSASIA, an organization that strives to improve people’s lives through sharing open technologies and fostering global connections and sustainable production. She serves as a member of the IEEE Standards Association Board of Governors and as vice chair of the Open Source Committee. She is also a board member of the Open Source Business Alliance and the Open Source Initiative. With over a decade of open source expertise, she supports companies in their technology transition to open source and innersource development models. Her recent efforts focused on bringing open source hardware into production at scale.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Developing on Ubuntu with WSL Interoperability: Tips and Tricks 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/developing_on_ubuntu_with_wsl_interoperability_tips_and_tricks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 17:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/developing_on_ubuntu_with_wsl_interoperability_tips_and_tricks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This session will provide the practical considerations of developing on Ubuntu on WSL with WSL interoperability, providing attendees a better understanding of WSL interoperability when developing on Ubuntu on WSL.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/developing_on_ubuntu_with_wsl_interoperability_tips_and_tricks/Slide.pptx&#34;&gt;Get Slide(*.pptx)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Software Developer for Ubuntu on WSL and Ubuntu on Hyper-V, core maintainer for WSL Utilities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Engaging new l10n contributors through Open Source Contributhon 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/engaging_new_l10n_contributors_through_open_source_contributhon/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 17:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/engaging_new_l10n_contributors_through_open_source_contributhon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Last year, Ubuntu Korean LoCo participated &amp;ldquo;Open Source Contributhon&amp;rdquo;(Contribution + Marathon) as Ubuntu Korean L10n team to engage new l10n contributors.&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Open Source Contributhon&amp;rdquo; is an program led by a government agency, And more than 20 teams joined last year.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this session, We&amp;rsquo;ll introduce details about &amp;ldquo;Open Source Contributhon&amp;rdquo;(which is now &amp;ldquo;Open Source Contribution Academy&amp;rdquo;) and our experiences about the program as mentors and as mentees.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bokmi Han will introduce about the Open Source Contributhon program&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Survival of The Fittest: How Open-source Helps Me Survive after Company Shutdown 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/survival_of_the_fittest_how_open_source_helps_me_survive_after_company_shutdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 16:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/survival_of_the_fittest_how_open_source_helps_me_survive_after_company_shutdown/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A year ago, I was still actively working as a general manager in a tour &amp;amp; travel company. At the beginning of the pandemic, my company minimized activity and created new services to survive the pandemic. However, at the end of the day, we have to face the reality: we have to shut down the company because our company relies on mobility and physical activity which currently has to be limited.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hacking on UnityX and building Ubuntu Remixes
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/hacking_on_unity7_and_unityx/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 16:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/hacking_on_unity7_and_unityx/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ll first be showing how to set up a build environment for UnityX. I&amp;rsquo;ll also demonstrate how to do a Merge Request on GitLab and package UnityX using qckdeb. We recently released our ISO builder for anyone to use it for creating Ubuntu remix ISOs. I&amp;rsquo;ll be demonstrating how easy it is to use the builder by creating an Ubuntu Remix live using UnityX.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/ubuntu-unity/ubuntu-remixes/ubuntu-unityx&#34;&gt;UnityX repo on GitLab&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m an official Ubuntu Member and the creator and project lead of Ubuntu Unity and Ubuntu Web Remix.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Who &#39;kill&#39;ed my processes? 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/who_killed_my_processes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 15:45:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/who_killed_my_processes/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;All of sudden, one of your processes that should be alive was &amp;lsquo;kill&amp;rsquo;ed by someone&amp;rsquo;s Signal! Who did that? Let&amp;rsquo;s trace the issue with Linux Kernel hacking.&#xA;In this session, I will talk about a real-life issue I met while working and attendees would learn about where to start if they want to trace signals through Kernel.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Attendees at least should know what the Signal is in Computer Science.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/who_killed_my_processes/session_who_killed_my_processes-leesoo_ahn.pptx&#34;&gt;Get Slide(*.pptx)&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>CI/CD with Snap package deployment 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/cicd_with_snap_package_deployment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 15:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/cicd_with_snap_package_deployment/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sponsored session (Ubuntu)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Build, test and publish applications automatically. Bring CI/CD to your IoT andappliances. Give your developers a pipeline to deliver updates to customersstraight from their standard process, and empower customers to test beta andpre-release versions. Whether you’re using Git with Travis or Jenkins,automated snap creation is just a few steps away. For open source projects, wewill even build your snap for ARM, x86, POWER and Z. Canary updates and automaticrollbacks let you go fast with confidence.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Desktop Ubuntu on Laptops/RaspberryPis - practices how to use it with SD cards, how to manage UEFI and more 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/desktop_ubuntu_on_laptopsraspberrypis___practices_how_to_use_it_with_sd_cards_how_to_manage_uefi_and_more/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 15:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/desktop_ubuntu_on_laptopsraspberrypis___practices_how_to_use_it_with_sd_cards_how_to_manage_uefi_and_more/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Desktop Ubuntu is a good use for workstations and some games development. I have tried for it not only software/hardware development but also game and daily use. Lately, we can use Chinese hackable PCs like GPD/Chuwi, which encourages &amp;lsquo;hacking.&amp;rsquo; - Firmware/OSes. We could customize such PCs for our use.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I will talk and discuss about my practice to use Ubuntu Desktop on Raspberry Pi and such &amp;lsquo;hackable&amp;rsquo; PCs.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to treat SD cards.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;How to hack UEFI to optimize PC&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Games on Ubuntu Desktop&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ubuntu Desktop and Raspberry Pi&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;and more&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Masafumi is now leading the Raspberry Pi community in Japan and volunteering Raspberry Pi Foundation since 2012 from the farthest eastern country &amp;lsquo;Japan.&amp;rsquo; Now, he moderates the Japanese language category on Raspberry Pi&amp;rsquo;s official forum.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Sinau Bash&#34; Program for Learning Bash Commands 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/sinau_bash_program_for_learning_bash_commands/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 14:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/sinau_bash_program_for_learning_bash_commands/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div style=&#34;position: relative; padding-bottom: 56.25%; height: 0; overflow: hidden;&#34;&gt;&#xA;      &lt;iframe allow=&#34;accelerometer; autoplay; clipboard-write; encrypted-media; gyroscope; picture-in-picture; web-share&#34; allowfullscreen=&#34;allowfullscreen&#34; loading=&#34;eager&#34; referrerpolicy=&#34;strict-origin-when-cross-origin&#34; src=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/embed/c_6cZ6uL5MM?autoplay=0&amp;controls=1&amp;end=0&amp;loop=0&amp;mute=0&amp;start=0&#34; style=&#34;position: absolute; top: 0; left: 0; width: 100%; height: 100%; border:0;&#34; title=&#34;YouTube video&#34;&#xA;      &gt;&lt;/iframe&gt;&#xA;    &lt;/div&gt;&#xA;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Bash is considered a difficult language for some people to learn. In general, bash language itself is used by people who work in the field of servers. People who work in the server field will be very helpful with the bash language because bash can run many commands on the server or can run commands automatically. For example, bash language is used in Ubuntu Server. In addition to the bash language server, it can be used in making programs, namely &amp;ldquo;Sinau Bash&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How Ubuntu empowers databases and cloud development on Azure 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/how_ubuntu_empowers_databases_and_cloud_development_on_azure/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 14:15:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/how_ubuntu_empowers_databases_and_cloud_development_on_azure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sponsored Session (Microsoft)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In this workshop, you will learn or ask your questions on how to deploy SQL Server on Linux 2019 and run a web application on a new Azure Linux virtual machine by following a great Microsoft Learn module: &lt;a href=&#34;https://aka.ms/LearnAzureAtUbuConAsia&#34;&gt;https://aka.ms/LearnAzureAtUbuConAsia&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Pre-requisites:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Experience using Bash from the command-line&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Familiarity or interest in using JavaScript to connect a database and/or build web applications&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Have you already finished this module? No worries, you can discuss anything what you want regarding this module even you already experienced. During the workshop, the speaker will explain general concept to better understand this Learn module with Microsoft open source approach with Ubuntu Linux &amp;amp; SQL Server on Linux 2019 and discuss with Q&amp;amp;As while workshop attendees are doing this Learn module.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Keynote - Ubuntu Desktop 21.10
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/keynote___flutter_for_linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 13:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/keynote___flutter_for_linux/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ken VanDine, Engineering Manager at Ubuntu Desktop, Canonical, would like to give you some story about What&amp;rsquo;s new on latest release of Ubuntu, Flutter for Linux support with new Ubuntu Installer built with Flutter. He would also like to share you what happened on Ubuntu community team since the team has been rebooted.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ken VanDine is an Engineering Manager at Canonical, leading the Ubuntu Desktop team. Ken has been involved in open source for over 20 years and is passionate about helping new developers get involved in open source. In Ken&amp;rsquo;s spare time he volunteers at Kramden Institute, refurbishing computers for underprivileged children and teaching middle school-aged children how to code.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome and Opening Remarks 
</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/welcome_and_opening_remarks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2021 13:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sessions/welcome_and_opening_remarks/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This session will cover how and why we have organized the first UbuCon Asia event. We&amp;rsquo;ll also introduce our host organizing communities, sponsors and partner communities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-the-speaker&#34;&gt;About the speaker&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Community Leader and Organizer at Ubuntu Korea Community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Junior DevOps Engineer at Cloudmate&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Studies Software engineering at Sungkonghoe University&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National IT Industry Promotion Agency of Korea (NIPA) is a Bronze Sponsor for Ubucon Asia 2021!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-18-nipa-kr-bronze-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 14:49:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-18-nipa-kr-bronze-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Logo of NIPA&#34; src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-18-nipa-kr-bronze-sponsor/logo.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are proud to announce that the &lt;strong&gt;National IT Industry Promotion Agency of Korea (NIPA)&lt;/strong&gt; is a &lt;strong&gt;Bronze Sponsor&lt;/strong&gt; for Ubucon Asia 2021!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NIPA is a national organisation in Korea that actively supports and promotes open source software development. It strengthens software development and provides industry support in a multitude of ways.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NIPA is devoted to reinforcing the competitiveness of the ICT industry and contributes to national economic growth through efficient support and laying the groundwork for industrial technology promotion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft has joined as a Gold Sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-08-microsoft-joins-as-gold-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 20:49:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-08-microsoft-joins-as-gold-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Logo of Microsoft&#34; src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-08-microsoft-joins-as-gold-sponsor/logo.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are proud to announce Microsoft as a Gold Sponsor for Ubucon Asia 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft requires no introduction in the technology world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Azure cloud, hybrid cloud and on-premise technologies are leaders in software as a service (SaaS), platform as a service (PaaS) and infrastructure as a service (IaaS).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Did you know that Ubuntu-based workloads are among the fastest growing on Microsoft Azure? Their partnership with Canonical has delivered an Azure-optimized kernel, improved performance, advanced security, automatic patching and updates, and flexible pricing options for Ubuntu on Azure as well as open source communities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networking on Gather Town space</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-05-networking-on-gather-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 23:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-05-networking-on-gather-town/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! The first UbuCon Asia coming in less then a month!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On this first UbuCon Asia, We&amp;rsquo;ll also have an additional virtual space: Gather Town space&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;ll use both Eventyay and Gather Town.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Eventyay for ticketing, timetable, video conference calls and Sponsor/Partner Community information page(Exhibition page)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Gather Town space for Virtual booth(for sponsors and partner communities) and Networking between attendees!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since we made decision on this very recently, Other then Virtual booth details, We don&amp;rsquo;t have plans on other details yet.&#xA;But, The event is just around the corner! So we&amp;rsquo;re working with content team to bring ideas on Gather space map design quickly.&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;ll give you more updates if we have some progress on building gather space.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudmate joins as our Silver sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-08-10-cloudmate-joins-as-silver-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 01:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-08-10-cloudmate-joins-as-silver-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Logo of Cloudmate&#34; src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-08-10-cloudmate-joins-as-silver-sponsor/logo.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are gladly to announce &lt;strong&gt;Cloudmate&lt;/strong&gt; as our part of &lt;strong&gt;Silver Sponsor&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloudmate is an certified CSP(Cloud Service Provider) company in Seoul, South Korea. They provides professional managed service on cloud environment. Based on experiences from MNCs, Cloudmate has its best certified engineers and developers in the cloud sector.&#xA;Through the professional managed service, Cloudmate supports systematic management and its cloud infrastructure to the customers. Furthermore, Cloudmate also offers consulting for cloud service to industries that are adapting cloud infrastructure for the first time.&#xA;Lastly, With Microsoft Azure MVP, Cloudmate has been contributed educational programs and activities to various vendors and many communities for years.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello UbuCon Asia speakers!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-30-speaker-schedules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 12:47:39 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-30-speaker-schedules/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello UbuCon Asia 2021 speakers!&#xA;Thanks again for submitting your proposals for the first UbuCon Asia!&#xA;We just completed reviewing proposals and now reaching out each person to confirm speaker participation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;confirm-your-participation&#34;&gt;Confirm your participation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your proposal was accepted, We&amp;rsquo;ll send you an email to confirm whether you&amp;rsquo;ll give speech on the event.&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://eventyay.com/my-sessions&#34;&gt;You may also check eventyay&lt;/a&gt; to see whether your proposal was accepted.&#xA;To confirm your speaker participation, simply reply us and tell us you will participate as speaker.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank you to Ubuntu for Join as Diamond Sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-24-ubuntu-joins-as-diamond-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 01:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-24-ubuntu-joins-as-diamond-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Logo of Ubuntu - Delivered by Canonical&#34; src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-24-ubuntu-joins-as-diamond-sponsor/delivered-by_black-orange_hex.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are gladly to announce Ubuntu as our part of &lt;strong&gt;Diamond Sponsor&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Ubuntu desktop as we know is the world&amp;rsquo;s most widely used Linux workstation platform, powering the work of engineers across the globe. Ubuntu today has many flavours and dozens of specialized derivatives. All share common infrastructure and software, making Ubuntu a unique single platform that scales from consumer electronics to the desktop and up into the cloud for enterprise computing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling for speakers is now closed!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-15-cfs-is-now-closed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:22:07 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-15-cfs-is-now-closed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello folks! &lt;strong&gt;Calling for speakers is now closed!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to everyone who submitted session proposals to the first Ubuntu conference in Asia!&#xA;We have received &lt;strong&gt;total 46 proposals!&lt;/strong&gt; This includes&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Talks &amp;amp; Extended Talks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lightning talks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Workshops&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Panel discussions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But this does not includes social events and sponsor sessions yet.&#xA;In next 2 weeks, Our content team will review your submissions until the end of this month.&#xA;Content team folks may contact to each person who submitted proposals to ask some further details.&#xA;If our content team people ask you some quesionts regarding your submissoins, please provide answers so that they can understand your submissions as much as they can!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double check your proposal submissions before deadline</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-11-double-check-proposal-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 15:34:54 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-11-double-check-proposal-submission/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Call for speakers will close soon on July 14th 23:59 UTC+9! If you have submitted any session proposals, please double check your submissions and update it if required before the deadline comes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;your-speaker-info&#34;&gt;Your speaker info&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please see the image and description below and check your speaker info submissions once again to see if anything missing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Name: Your full name (e.g. Youngbin Han)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Email: Your email contact address. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive proposal review result with the email address you entered here. (e.g. &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:hello@world.com&#34;&gt;hello@world.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Position: What you do on the organisation you&amp;rsquo;re in (e.g. Community Organiser, Developer, Engineer, Student, Founder, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Organisation: Company, School, Community, or other type of organisation you&amp;rsquo;re participating&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Country: Country or region you live in (e.g. South Korea, Japan, China, Taiwan, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Short Biography: Short introduction about yourself&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Photo: Upload your profile photo&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Website, GitHub, Facebook, Twitter, Linkedin: Enter your social media information (Optional)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Timezone: Your Timezone information. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to provide this info! Used for scheduling your session! (e.g. UTC+9)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-11-double-check-proposal-submission/speaker_info.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling for proposals extended by July 14</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-30-cfp-extended-by-july-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 08:31:29 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-30-cfp-extended-by-july-14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you have been rush into submitting proposal, You now have extra 2 more weeks to finalize submitting your proposlas!&#xA;UbuCon Asia 2021 Calling for proposal due date has been extended by &lt;strong&gt;July 14th 23:59 (UTC+9).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For your informations, See details you need know from below before submitting proposals.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Please do not hesitate to contact Ubucon Asia team whether through social media or email if you are not sure about writing your proposal or preparing your presentation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become our individual patron today</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-24-donation-ticket/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:20:21 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-24-donation-ticket/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Tickets&#34; src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-24-donation-ticket/tickets.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To raise enough amount of money required stably, We&amp;rsquo;re announcing another way to contribute on our event.&#xA;From today, You can contribute to our successful event by becoming one of our individual patrons!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To become our patron, Visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://eventyay.com/e/75ac7f83&#34;&gt;our event page on eventyay.com&lt;/a&gt; and follow steps below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sign in with your eventyay.com account.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Scroll down to &amp;ldquo;Tickets&amp;rdquo; section, You will see &amp;ldquo;Sign Up to Join Ubucon Asia 2021&amp;rdquo; which is free ticket and &amp;ldquo;Donation Ticket&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set price of donation ticket you would like to donate. (You can set amount between 50 USD ~ 500 USD)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set quantity of donation ticket. And Click &amp;ldquo;Order now&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On next screen, fill in the &amp;ldquo;Ticket Holder&amp;rsquo;s Information&amp;rdquo; form. If you need, Check &amp;ldquo;Enable Billing Information&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On &amp;ldquo;Payment Method&amp;rdquo; choose Paypal. (which is the only payment option you will found) and then click &amp;ldquo;Proceed to Checkout&amp;rdquo; to continue&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On next screen, confirm payment information. Then Click the yellow &amp;ldquo;Pay with PayPal&amp;rdquo; button.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You should now see PayPal payment dialog. (On bottom, You should be able to see &amp;ldquo;Cancel and return to FOSSASIA PTE. LTD.&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To make payment, Sign in with your PayPal account to make payment, or just choose &amp;ldquo;Pay with a Card&amp;rdquo; to pay without PayPal account.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;After succesful payment, you will be able to download invoice, see payment result, and cancel order in case if you want.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To purchase donation ticket, You will need a debit or credit card that PayPal supports.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Proposals</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-30-calling-for-proposals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:39:21 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-30-calling-for-proposals/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;UbuCon Asia 2021 team have been calling for speakers, volunteers, sponsors and community partners from earlier this month.&#xA;As this is the first time to organize UbuCon Asia, Our proposal period is relatively longer then other conferences.&#xA;This is a reminder post that includes all details for each items and URL link to them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;calling-for-speakers&#34;&gt;Calling for speakers&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Submit until June 30th 2021, Session acceptance will be on July 30th 2021&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Session type: Talk(30min, 45min), Lightning talk(5min), Workshop(1hour, 2hour), Panel duscussions(55mins)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All session duration includes time for question and answer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;For &amp;ldquo;Talk&amp;rdquo; type session, you can submit pre-recorded session. You still exprected to present on the room on your session time to answer questions from attendees.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;For pre-recorded talks, You can submit session in Korean, Japanese, Chinese(China), Chinese(Taiwan), Cantonese(Hong Kong) and Indonesia&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../2021-05-05-call-for-speakers&#34;&gt;See Calling for speakers details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/cfs/&#34;&gt;Submit your session on eventyay.com - Sign up/Sign in for eventyay.com required&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.ubuntu.com/UbuconAsia/2021/SessionIdeas&#34;&gt;Session topic ideas that might help you to choose topic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Inquiries: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:content@ubucon.asia&#34;&gt;content@ubucon.asia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;calling-for-video-translation-volunteers&#34;&gt;Calling for video translation volunteers&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Submit until June 30th 2021, Application result will be announced on July 30th 2021&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Help us to translate Non-English pre-recorded session into English&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Korean, Japanese, Chinese(China), Chinese(Taiwan), Cantonese(Hong Kong) and Indonesia&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll use some automation tools (Speech to text, Translation API) to automate our jobs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../2021-05-05-calling-for-translation-volunteers&#34;&gt;See Calling for translation volunteers details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/3qJwwiKdKsUTKFLB8&#34;&gt;Submit volunteer application&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Inquiries: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:contact@ubucon.asia&#34;&gt;contact@ubucon.asia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;calling-for-sponsors&#34;&gt;Calling for sponsors&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Although it&amp;rsquo;s a fully virtual event, We still need help from sponsors to make this event actually happen.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Become our sponsor, and let&amp;rsquo;s shape out the first UbuCon Asia event!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/&#34;&gt;See sponsorship program details and sponsorship brochure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Contact us to become our sponsor: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sponsorship@ubucon.asia&#34;&gt;sponsorship@ubucon.asia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;calling-for-partner-communities&#34;&gt;Calling for partner communities&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To promote UbuCon Asia event across Asia much further, We’re looking for partner communities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your community will collaborate with UbuCon Asia team to cross-promote each other’s community and event.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/join-as-partner-community/&#34;&gt;See partner community program details and brochure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Contact us to become our partner community: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:contact@ubucon.asia&#34;&gt;contact@ubucon.asia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Video Translation Volunteers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-calling-for-translation-volunteers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 12:01:51 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-calling-for-translation-volunteers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As we begin &lt;a href=&#34;../2021-05-05-call-for-speakers&#34;&gt;calling for speakers&lt;/a&gt;, We&amp;rsquo;re now also calling for translation volunteers from today.&#xA;Translation volunteers will colloborate local community to &lt;strong&gt;translate pre-recorded sessions from following languages to English.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Korean - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Korea Community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Japanese - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Japanese Community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chinese(China) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu China Community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chinese(Taiwan) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Taiwan Community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cantonese(Hong Kong) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Hong Kong Community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Indonesian - You will collaborate GNOME Indonesia and Openstack Indonesia&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will use speech-to-text and machine translation tool to automate subtitle works. But there will be still many things to fix. therefore, help from volunteers are still required.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Speakers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-call-for-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 09:50:20 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-call-for-speakers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The first Ubuntu Conference in Asia (Ubucon Asia 2021) is four months ahead!&#xA;Ubucon Asia 2021 Call for Speakers is now open until 30 June, and talks acceptance will be on 30 July.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the reference topics for you to discuss in Ubucon Asia 2021:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Desktop&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Server/Infrastructure/Cloud&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Windows Subsystem for Linux(WSL)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Localization(L10n)/Fonts/Input Methods&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Internet of Things(IoT)/Embedded&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Security&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Community/Social Context&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Case Studies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have some sessions to talk with two days event. We usually recommend to give presentation in English. But GOOD NEWS if you are not confident with your English, for Talks and Panels you may consider to give presentation in following languages (Korean, Japanese, Chinese(China), Chinese(Taiwan), Cantonese(Hong Kong), Indonesia).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubucon Asia 2021 Plan updates</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-04-21-some-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:10:16 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-04-21-some-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been about 3 months after I published post &lt;a href=&#34;../2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Looking for organizers&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;.&#xA;Last 3 months, many Ubuntu Local communities and other FLOSS communities contact me to join Ubucon Asia 2021 team.&#xA;Today, We have 12 host communities from 10 different regions in the team. Some organizers from those communities with excellent experience with organizing international events also joined our team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And with this Ubucon Asia 2021 team, We&amp;rsquo;ve been made many progress until now. Today I would like to share some planned schedules of upcoming Ubucon Asia 2021.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for organizers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 01:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In Asia, You can find various community conferences about open source and linux that covers Asia region. Good examples of this are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;openSUSE.Asia&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;GNOME.Asia&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;LibreOffice Asia Conference&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;PyCon APAC&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;FOSSASIA Summit&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;and more&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For past a few years, when I was the leader of Ubuntu Korea Community, I attended several conferences overseas to not just meet and learn but also to interact with Ubuntu local communities overseas. Especially, communities located near South Korea region.&#xA;By attending overseas events, I could interact with people from various open source communities from manu different regions.&#xA;But, Unfortunately, I could rarely meet people from Ubuntu local communities. Also, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find Ubuntu conference or event for Asia region.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>.NET DEV</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/dotnetdevkr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/dotnetdevkr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;.Net Dev is a local .Net user group in South Korea.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Our community members are especially interested in .NET development and its ecosystem.&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Including ASP.NET, EF, Blazor, etc&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We runs regular local conference called &amp;ldquo;.NET Conf x Seoul&amp;rdquo; every year and &amp;ldquo;.NET Conf Mini&amp;rdquo; almost every quarter.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;.NET Conf Korea by .NET Dev: &lt;a href=&#34;https://dotnetconf.kr&#34;&gt;https://dotnetconf.kr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;.NET Medium Blog: &lt;a href=&#34;https://blog.dotnetdev.kr&#34;&gt;https://blog.dotnetdev.kr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;.NET Dev Discourse: &lt;a href=&#34;https://forum.dotnetdev.kr&#34;&gt;https://forum.dotnetdev.kr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About Ubucon Asia 2021</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome, and thank you for your interest on Ubucon Asia.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ubucon Asia is an event organized by Ubuntu Communities in Asia.&#xA;It&amp;rsquo;s for everyone who involved with or interested in Ubuntu, Linux and other Free and Open source technologies.&#xA;Ubucon Asia is also a place for Ubuntu people from Asia to connect, learn, and share their knowlegdes each other.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ubucon Asia 2021, the first Ubuntu conference in Asia will be a virtual conference driven by multiple Ubuntu LoCos from Asia.&#xA;Participate the first Ubucon Asia from your home, and get connected to Ubuntu Community around the world.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become a sponsor</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your interest in Ubuntu and Ubucon Asia.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;As a non-profit and community organized event, Even Ubucon Asia 2021 is fully virtual event,&#xA;We still need support from sponsors to make the event happen.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;By becoming one of our sponsors, you are directly contributing to research and development of Ubuntu and Open Source Software, and also making Open Source Community more active and sustainable.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Your contribution makes it possible for us to bring a large number of Ubuntu users and contributors across Asia to connect, interact, help and learn together. It will also grow not just the global Ubuntu communities but also Ubuntu local communities around Asia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudmate</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/cloudmate/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/cloudmate/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Cloudmate is the certified CSP company that located in Seoul, Korea.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloudmate provides professional managed service on cloud environment. Based on experiences from MNCs, Cloudmate has its best certified engineers and developers in the cloud sector.&#xA;Through the professional managed service, Cloudmate supports systematic management and its cloud infrastructure to the customers. Furthermore, Cloudmate also offers consulting for cloud service to industries that are adapting cloud infrastructure for the first time.&#xA;Lastly, With Microsoft Azure MVP, Cloudmate has been contributed educational programs and activities to various vendors and many communities for years.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Debian Malaysia</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/debian-malaysia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/debian-malaysia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Malaysian Debian GNU/Linux enthusiasts community&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;You can be reach us by various means:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chat: Telegram group (&lt;a href=&#34;https://t.me/debianmalaysia&#34;&gt;https://t.me/debianmalaysia&lt;/a&gt;) / IRC &lt;code&gt;#debian-malaysia&lt;/code&gt; on Freenode / Matrix &lt;code&gt;/join #freenode_#debian-malaysia:matrix.org&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Website: &lt;a href=&#34;http://debianmalaysia.gitlab.io&#34;&gt;http://debianmalaysia.gitlab.io&lt;/a&gt; (mirror: &lt;a href=&#34;https://malaysia-team.pages.debian.net&#34;&gt;https://malaysia-team.pages.debian.net&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Mailing lists: Debmal google group (&lt;a href=&#34;https://groups.google.com/g/debmal&#34;&gt;https://groups.google.com/g/debmal&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Social media: Twitter - &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/debianmalaysia&#34;&gt;https://twitter.com/debianmalaysia&lt;/a&gt; / Mastodon - &lt;a href=&#34;https://linuxrocks.online/@debianmalaysia&#34;&gt;https://linuxrocks.online/@debianmalaysia&lt;/a&gt; (both cross-posted)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please choose what ever communication channel and you are welcome!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eventyay</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/eventyay/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/eventyay/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Eventyay is an open source event management solution that comes with a variety of features including Call for Speakers, Scheduling, Registration, Payment Gateways, Video Integration (Jitsi, BigBlueButton, custom video platform) and more. Support us, support open source by using Eventyay for your event, report bugs, or even fix them yourself :)&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Code &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/fossasia/open-event-frontend&#34;&gt;https://github.com/fossasia/open-event-frontend&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Support Page &lt;a href=&#34;http://support.eventyay.com&#34;&gt;http://support.eventyay.com&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOSS Nepal Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/foss-np/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/foss-np/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FOSS Nepal Community is a team of volunteers who believe in the usage of Free/Open Source Software (FOSS). The primary objective of the community is to promote, develop and diversify the usage of Free/Open Source Software in Nepal.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To raise awareness among general public, government bodies, private sector, civil society, educational institutions and media for expanding the scope of Information and Communication Technology (ICT) via Free and Open Source Software&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To sensitize general public, government bodies, civil society and media for the implementation of e-governance by means of FOSS; the optimal solution for e-governance&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Advocacy for alternatives in Intellectual Property Rights (IPR) specific to ICT&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To enhance the capacity of IT professionals by promoting inclusion of Free and Open Source Software in educational system and providing platform for IT professionals to make them globally saleable.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To develop, modify and localize Free and Open Source Software to address local software need.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>FOSSASIA</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/fossasia/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/fossasia/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;FOSSASIA develops Open Source software and hardware solutions with a global developer community from its base in Asia and organizes Open Technology events around the year. The organization also runs coding programs and development contests.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The annual FOSSASIA Summit is the premier Open Technology event in Asia for developers, start-ups, and contributors. It is a unique opportunity to share knowledge and experience about Open Source and meet interesting contributors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;FOSSASIA was founded in 2009 by Mario Behling and Hong Phuc Dang.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Gimpscape ID</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/gimpscape-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/gimpscape-id/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Gimpscape ID community is a one of design community from Indonesia that has oriented to the use of Free/Open Source Software (FOSS). On various occasions, Gimpscape ID always strives to contribute to activities related to free/open source software.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Telegram &lt;a href=&#34;https://t.me/gimpscape&#34;&gt;https://t.me/gimpscape&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Instagram https://instagram/gimpscape_id&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>GNOME Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/gnome-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/gnome-id/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GNOME Indonesia (GNOME-ID) is a non-profit community founded to support the use, promotion and assistance of users of the GNOME desktop environment in Indonesia.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Join as Partner Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/join-as-partner-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/join-as-partner-community/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;To promote UbuCon Asia event across Asia much further, We’re looking for partner communities.&#xA;By becoming our partner community, Your community will collaborate with UbuCon Asia team to cross-promote each other’s community and event.&#xA;This will be a big help for both partner communities and UbuCon Asia to connect with even more diverse people and encourage them to participate and engage.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To learn more about our partner community program, please refer to our brochure.&#xA;To become our partner community, please contact Coordination team. &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:contact@ubucon.asia&#34;&gt;contact@ubucon.asia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>KLAS (Kelompok Linux Arek Suroboyo)</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/klas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/klas/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Arek Suroboyo Linux Group (Surabaya Linux User Group) (KLAS) is one of the Linux user groups in the city of Surabaya. We have been around since 1995, and are still active today. We have several routine agendas and facilities that we do and until now we have facilitated them to support Go FOSS activities in Surabaya, such as:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cangkrukan KLAS&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Local Conferences (Open Infrastucture Day 2019)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;International Conferences (openSUSE.Asia Summit 2019, GNOME.Asia Summit 2019, LibreOffice Conference 2019)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Website : &lt;a href=&#34;https://klas.or.id/&#34;&gt;https://klas.or.id/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Shortner Link : s.klas.or.id&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Facebook : &lt;a href=&#34;http://fb.com/kelompoklinuxareksuroboyo&#34;&gt;http://fb.com/kelompoklinuxareksuroboyo&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Instagram : instagram.com/klas_activity (@klas_activity)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Twitter : @klas_activity&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;LinkedIn : Kelompok Linux Arek Suroboyo&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/microsoft/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/microsoft/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Our mission is to empower every person and every organization on the planet to achieve more.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ubuntu-based workloads are among the fastest growing on Azure. Microsoft has partnered with Canonical to deliver an Azure-optimized kernel, improved performance, advanced security, automatic patching and updates, and flexible pricing options for Ubuntu on Azure as well as open source communities.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/ubuntu/?ocid=AID3035196&#34;&gt;Click here to learn more about &lt;strong&gt;Ubuntu on Azure&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;booth-event-at-gather-town&#34;&gt;Booth event at Gather Town&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;korean-attendees&#34;&gt;Korean attendees&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Participate survey event on the left of our booth.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National IT Industry Promotion Agency of Korea</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/nipa-kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/nipa-kr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;openup---open-source-software-promotion-organization-at-nipa&#34;&gt;OpenUP - Open source software promotion organization at NIPA&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are an institution that strengthens open source SW development capabilities and helps domestic IT and industries develop in various ways.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;nipa---national-it-industry-promotion-agency-of-korea&#34;&gt;NIPA - National IT Industry Promotion Agency of Korea&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NIPA devotes itself to reinforcing the competitiveness of the ICT industry and contributes to the economic growth through the efficient support and laying the groundwork for the industrial technology promotion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenStack Indonesia Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/openstack-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/openstack-id/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;OpenStack Indonesia (OS-ID) is an official OpenStack community (under Open Infrastructure Foundation) based in Indonesia. This community was established for all Indonesians who are interested in OpenStack projects/services.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2019, we held the first official community meetup in Jakarta and repeated monthly in several cities around Indonesia. First Indonesia Open Infrastructure Day was successfully held in November 2019 in Surabaya, and Last 2020 held the Open Infrastructure Day Indonesia event virtually.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>OpenStack Korea User Group</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/openstack-kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/openstack-kr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;OpenStack is cloud operating system which can manage massive computing in data center, storage, network resource and provisioning by APIs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;As an official user group, OpenStack Korea Community actively engages with many OpenStack users and interested people through various communication channels such as Facebook, mailing list, IRC, and Slack (sign up), as well as various regular seminars, study activities, and translation team activities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;OpenStack Korea Community held 1st OpenStack Day Korea event in 2014, and has held events every year.&#xA;In 2020, Open Infrastructure Community Days 2020 was held with Kubernetes Korea Group, Korea Ceph User Group, and OCP Korea Community.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Canonical is the publisher of Ubuntu, the OS for most public cloud workloads as well as the emerging categories of smart gateways, self-driving cars, and advanced robots. Canonical provides enterprise security, support, and services to commercial users of Ubuntu.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu China Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-cn/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-cn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ubuntu China LoCo Team is an official local community in China approved by Ubuntu Community Council.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In 2005, the Ubuntu community in China started to form a team to take care of localization efforts of Ubuntu and the team soon transformed into an active community to promote Ubuntu and attract new comers. The Ubuntu China LoCo Team have so far organized over 100 local Ubuntu events and even more joint events, with very wide cooperation with academic institutions and commercial companies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Hong Kong Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-hk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-hk/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ubuntu LoCo Hong Kong Team is a group of volunteers come together to share, enjoy, advocate and promote the usage of Ubuntu Linux in Hong Kong. The team will help to raise a local community and help others resolving difficulties when using Ubuntu Linux.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Japanese Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-jp/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-jp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ubuntu Japanese Team is voluntary group that intent improving and expanding Ubuntu in Japan, and is verified as an official Ubuntu LoCo till 2005.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Korea Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-kr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ubuntu Korea Community is an official verified LoCo(Local Community) Team by Ubuntu Community Council in South Korea.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Ubuntu Korean community started in 2005, very small. But it&amp;rsquo;s now one of the most active Open Source communities in South Korea. We are continuing to carry out activities that can be helpful to Ubuntu users in Korea and broadly to people related to IT in Korea.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We hold various seminars, conferences, community-driven projects, joint seminars with other communities, and contribution workshops every year, and we also exchange with various overseas open source communities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Kylin</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-kylin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-kylin/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Ubuntu Kylin is an official flavor of Ubuntu.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It committed to bringing an easy, excellent, expert, and elaborate Linux distribution to users worldwide.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It integrates the independently developed UKUI desktop environment which adheres to the friendly and simple design, aka Ubuntu Kylin User Interface.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;It includes more than 20 applications developed for ordinary users to enjoy a pleasant life and easy office operating system experience.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Links to social media&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;GitHub: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/UbuntuKylin&#34;&gt;https://github.com/UbuntuKylin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;UKUI GitHub: &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/ukui&#34;&gt;https://github.com/ukui&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Twitter: &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/Ubuntu_Kylin&#34;&gt;https://twitter.com/Ubuntu_Kylin&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;YouTube: &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UClMqqFSY7qqakeumfAB8zbA&#34;&gt;https://www.youtube.com/channel/UClMqqFSY7qqakeumfAB8zbA&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Launchpad: &lt;a href=&#34;https://launchpad.net/~ubuntukylin-members/&#34;&gt;https://launchpad.net/~ubuntukylin-members/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Malaysia Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-my/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-my/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ubuntu Malaysia Local Community Started on July 2005, the Malaysian Team has been approved as official LoCo Team since 2009 and we have already grown to over 200 members. We aim to provide free community support to users of any of the Ubuntu flavours as well as advocating the use of Ubuntu to individuals and organizations a like.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The LoCo is meant for anyone residing in Malaysia who uses or is interested in Ubuntu. Everyone is welcome to join and contribute to the group regardless if you&amp;rsquo;re a Linux newbie or a well-known expert in the field.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Myanmar Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-mm/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-mm/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Note: Due to this local community&amp;rsquo;s country level situation, Ubuntu Myanmar Community is volunteering only when they have some chance to participate.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;/blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We, Ubuntu Myanmar Loco team is an Ubuntu Council-recognized Loco Team that is offering support in the ease use of Ubuntu Operating System in computers across Myanmar.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Ubuntu for Myanmar initiated action in 2009. It was a youth organization that had been continuously organizing Ubuntu and Ubuntu-related Open Source software events, free workshops and had been an active organization. It has been praised by the IT community and portrayed by the media as the most active organization facilitating several events.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Taiwan Local Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-tw/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/hosts/ubuntu-tw/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ubuntu Taiwan LoCo Team a.k.a Ubuntu-TW is a group of volunteers who enjoy Ubuntu and love to share, promote and make helps in Taiwan since 2005.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Our aim is make Ubuntu more easily to get start and more friendly to use for Traditional Chinese users.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We involving in localization, making workshop and collaborate with other FLOSS/Open-culture Communities like Mozilla Taiwan Community(MozTW), Open Culture Foundation(OCF), Linux user groups in Taiwan, etc.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;We also active on SNS and offline FLOSS event to gathering with people, and help them to get the solution using Ubuntu or solve their problem about using Ubuntu.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;In addition, we organizing Ubuntu Release Party twice every year regularly.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Unity Remix</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-unity-remix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-unity-remix/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Ubuntu Unity Remix is an Ubuntu remix (unofficial flavour) which uses Unity7 instead of gnome-shell.&#xA;The latest stable release of Ubuntu Unity is 21.04 and we are also working on the desktop successor of Unity7, UnityX.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Web: &lt;a href=&#34;https://ubuntuunity.org&#34;&gt;https://ubuntuunity.org&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Twitter: &lt;a href=&#34;https://twitter.com/ubuntu_unity&#34;&gt;https://twitter.com/ubuntu_unity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Telegram: &lt;a href=&#34;https://t.me/ubuntuunityannouncements&#34;&gt;https://t.me/ubuntuunityannouncements&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Discord: &lt;a href=&#34;https://discord.gg/M2AWuCK&#34;&gt;https://discord.gg/M2AWuCK&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;GitLab: &lt;a href=&#34;https://gitlab.com/ubuntu-unity&#34;&gt;https://gitlab.com/ubuntu-unity&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>UbuntuDDE Remix</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-dde-remix/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-dde-remix/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;UbuntuDDE Remix is a GNU/Linux distribution based on Ubuntu with the most beautiful desktop environment. It is a Remix flavor of Ubuntu desktop with Deepin Desktop Environment (DDE).&#xA;The initial release was 20.04 (focal) as the project got started during the first wave of Covid 19. It is not yet an official flavor recognized by Canonical Ltd. but the release schedule is aligned closely with the other Ubuntu flavors. The latest release of the UbuntuDDE Remix is 21.04 (Hirsute Hippo) which was launched in April, 2021.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Virtual Venue (Gather town)</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/venue/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/venue/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For Sponsor &amp;amp; Partner Community Virtual booth and To Socialize Attendees, We have Gather space for the event.&#xA;Hope you enjoy our Gather space, meet new people and also make new opportunities!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;entering-gather-space--going-back-to-eventyay&#34;&gt;Entering Gather space &amp;amp; Going back to Eventyay&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To join Gather space, Join the event room on eventyay first, Then click &amp;ldquo;Gather.town space&amp;rdquo; on sidebar. That brings you to Gather space.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To go back to eventyay video call, You may find dedicated areas for going back to eventyay. Move your avatar and press &lt;code&gt;X&lt;/code&gt; key to go back.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h1 id=&#34;virtual-booth&#34;&gt;Virtual Booth&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have virtual booth from our Sponsors and Partner Communities. Visit their booth and learn about them while booth is running.&#xA;Please note that booth hours are vary by each booth. Please refer to the table below for booth hours.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WhaTap Labs</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/whatap-labs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/whatap-labs/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;WhaTap Labs provides IT monitoring service &amp;ldquo;WhaTap&amp;rdquo;.&#xA;We make IT services easier and more reliable for developers and operators.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>WSLHUB (WSL Korea User Group)</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/wslhub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/wslhub/</guid>
      <description>&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;WSLHUB is a local user group community in South Korea.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Our community members are especially interested in WSL and the Linux Ecosystem.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Our community currently runs several open-source projects(such as WslManager, WslQuery) and a Facebook group to communicate with our members.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
