<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Ubucon Asia 2021</title>
    <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Ubucon Asia 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 23:30:00 +0900</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>UbuCon Asia 2021 Final report</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-12-01-ubucon-asia-2021-final-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Dec 2021 23:30:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-12-01-ubucon-asia-2021-final-report/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It’s been about a year since we started to gather organizers, form a team. And last September, with a lot of support from Ubuntu Community and other many Free and Open Source Communities around Asia, We successfully organized the first UbuCon Asia which was a virtual event.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;With this report, We would like to wrap-up and finalize our event activities for this year. Then we would like to think about how we can do better at the next UbuCon Asia. We hope this report would be helpful for other Ubuntu community folks who would like to organize similar events.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Swag updates</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-10-20-swag-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-10-20-swag-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Swags - Zipup hoodie, T-Shirt and Stickers!&#34; src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-10-20-swag-updates/swags.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;free-swags-updates&#34;&gt;Free swags updates&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We&amp;rsquo;re currently distributing swags of UbuCon Asia 2021! For Organizers, Speakers, Patrons and Volunteers, We already distributed E-Gift cards via email that can be redeemed on out Swag shop. Swags for Sponsors (5 Qty for each) and Attendees (One for each) who won for swag lottery or found treasure during treasure hunt will be also distributed soon. It will take about 1~2 weeks to proceed with purchasing E-Gift cards and distributing via email.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubucon Asia 2021 - YouTube Premiere Restream - 9-10 Oct, 2021</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-10-05-restream-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-10-05-restream-schedule/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Thank you once again to everyone who took part in the first Ubucon Asia 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thank you so much to our speakers, who spent a great deal of time preparing their wonderful presentations. For anyone who missed any of them, or would like to watch them again, we are announcing that they will be restreamed on YouTube on 9-10 Oct 2021 and will thereafter be available to watch on demand. Details are below.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>National IT Industry Promotion Agency of Korea (NIPA) is a Bronze Sponsor for Ubucon Asia 2021!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-18-nipa-kr-bronze-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 14:49:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-18-nipa-kr-bronze-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Logo of NIPA&#34; src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-18-nipa-kr-bronze-sponsor/logo.jpg&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are proud to announce that the &lt;strong&gt;National IT Industry Promotion Agency of Korea (NIPA)&lt;/strong&gt; is a &lt;strong&gt;Bronze Sponsor&lt;/strong&gt; for Ubucon Asia 2021!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NIPA is a national organisation in Korea that actively supports and promotes open source software development. It strengthens software development and provides industry support in a multitude of ways.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;NIPA is devoted to reinforcing the competitiveness of the ICT industry and contributes to national economic growth through efficient support and laying the groundwork for industrial technology promotion.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft has joined as a Gold Sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-08-microsoft-joins-as-gold-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 20:49:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-08-microsoft-joins-as-gold-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Logo of Microsoft&#34; src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-08-microsoft-joins-as-gold-sponsor/logo.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are proud to announce Microsoft as a Gold Sponsor for Ubucon Asia 2021.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Microsoft requires no introduction in the technology world.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Azure cloud, hybrid cloud and on-premise technologies are leaders in software as a service (SaaS), platform as a service (PaaS) and infrastructure as a service (IaaS).&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Did you know that Ubuntu-based workloads are among the fastest growing on Microsoft Azure? Their partnership with Canonical has delivered an Azure-optimized kernel, improved performance, advanced security, automatic patching and updates, and flexible pricing options for Ubuntu on Azure as well as open source communities.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Networking on Gather Town space</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-05-networking-on-gather-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 23:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-05-networking-on-gather-town/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hi everyone! The first UbuCon Asia coming in less then a month!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;On this first UbuCon Asia, We&amp;rsquo;ll also have an additional virtual space: Gather Town space&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;ll use both Eventyay and Gather Town.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Eventyay for ticketing, timetable, video conference calls and Sponsor/Partner Community information page(Exhibition page)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Gather Town space for Virtual booth(for sponsors and partner communities) and Networking between attendees!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Since we made decision on this very recently, Other then Virtual booth details, We don&amp;rsquo;t have plans on other details yet.&#xA;But, The event is just around the corner! So we&amp;rsquo;re working with content team to bring ideas on Gather space map design quickly.&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;ll give you more updates if we have some progress on building gather space.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Cloudmate joins as our Silver sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-08-10-cloudmate-joins-as-silver-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 01:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-08-10-cloudmate-joins-as-silver-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Logo of Cloudmate&#34; src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-08-10-cloudmate-joins-as-silver-sponsor/logo.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are gladly to announce &lt;strong&gt;Cloudmate&lt;/strong&gt; as our part of &lt;strong&gt;Silver Sponsor&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Cloudmate is an certified CSP(Cloud Service Provider) company in Seoul, South Korea. They provides professional managed service on cloud environment. Based on experiences from MNCs, Cloudmate has its best certified engineers and developers in the cloud sector.&#xA;Through the professional managed service, Cloudmate supports systematic management and its cloud infrastructure to the customers. Furthermore, Cloudmate also offers consulting for cloud service to industries that are adapting cloud infrastructure for the first time.&#xA;Lastly, With Microsoft Azure MVP, Cloudmate has been contributed educational programs and activities to various vendors and many communities for years.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hello UbuCon Asia speakers!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-30-speaker-schedules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 12:47:39 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-30-speaker-schedules/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello UbuCon Asia 2021 speakers!&#xA;Thanks again for submitting your proposals for the first UbuCon Asia!&#xA;We just completed reviewing proposals and now reaching out each person to confirm speaker participation.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;confirm-your-participation&#34;&gt;Confirm your participation&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;If your proposal was accepted, We&amp;rsquo;ll send you an email to confirm whether you&amp;rsquo;ll give speech on the event.&#xA;&lt;a href=&#34;https://eventyay.com/my-sessions&#34;&gt;You may also check eventyay&lt;/a&gt; to see whether your proposal was accepted.&#xA;To confirm your speaker participation, simply reply us and tell us you will participate as speaker.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Thank you to Ubuntu for Join as Diamond Sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-24-ubuntu-joins-as-diamond-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 01:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-24-ubuntu-joins-as-diamond-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Logo of Ubuntu - Delivered by Canonical&#34; src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-24-ubuntu-joins-as-diamond-sponsor/delivered-by_black-orange_hex.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We are gladly to announce Ubuntu as our part of &lt;strong&gt;Diamond Sponsor&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Ubuntu desktop as we know is the world&amp;rsquo;s most widely used Linux workstation platform, powering the work of engineers across the globe. Ubuntu today has many flavours and dozens of specialized derivatives. All share common infrastructure and software, making Ubuntu a unique single platform that scales from consumer electronics to the desktop and up into the cloud for enterprise computing.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling for speakers is now closed!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-15-cfs-is-now-closed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:22:07 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-15-cfs-is-now-closed/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hello folks! &lt;strong&gt;Calling for speakers is now closed!&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Thanks to everyone who submitted session proposals to the first Ubuntu conference in Asia!&#xA;We have received &lt;strong&gt;total 46 proposals!&lt;/strong&gt; This includes&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Talks &amp;amp; Extended Talks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Lightning talks&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Workshops&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Panel discussions&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;But this does not includes social events and sponsor sessions yet.&#xA;In next 2 weeks, Our content team will review your submissions until the end of this month.&#xA;Content team folks may contact to each person who submitted proposals to ask some further details.&#xA;If our content team people ask you some quesionts regarding your submissoins, please provide answers so that they can understand your submissions as much as they can!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Double check your proposal submissions before deadline</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-11-double-check-proposal-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 15:34:54 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-11-double-check-proposal-submission/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Call for speakers will close soon on July 14th 23:59 UTC+9! If you have submitted any session proposals, please double check your submissions and update it if required before the deadline comes.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;your-speaker-info&#34;&gt;Your speaker info&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Please see the image and description below and check your speaker info submissions once again to see if anything missing.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Name: Your full name (e.g. Youngbin Han)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Email: Your email contact address. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive proposal review result with the email address you entered here. (e.g. &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:hello@world.com&#34;&gt;hello@world.com&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Position: What you do on the organisation you&amp;rsquo;re in (e.g. Community Organiser, Developer, Engineer, Student, Founder, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Organisation: Company, School, Community, or other type of organisation you&amp;rsquo;re participating&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Country: Country or region you live in (e.g. South Korea, Japan, China, Taiwan, etc.)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Short Biography: Short introduction about yourself&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Photo: Upload your profile photo&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Website, GitHub, Facebook, Twitter, Linkedin: Enter your social media information (Optional)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Timezone: Your Timezone information. Don&amp;rsquo;t forget to provide this info! Used for scheduling your session! (e.g. UTC+9)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-11-double-check-proposal-submission/speaker_info.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling for proposals extended by July 14</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-30-cfp-extended-by-july-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 08:31:29 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-30-cfp-extended-by-july-14/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you have been rush into submitting proposal, You now have extra 2 more weeks to finalize submitting your proposlas!&#xA;UbuCon Asia 2021 Calling for proposal due date has been extended by &lt;strong&gt;July 14th 23:59 (UTC+9).&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For your informations, See details you need know from below before submitting proposals.&#xA;&lt;strong&gt;Please do not hesitate to contact Ubucon Asia team whether through social media or email if you are not sure about writing your proposal or preparing your presentation.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Become our individual patron today</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-24-donation-ticket/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:20:21 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-24-donation-ticket/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img alt=&#34;Tickets&#34; src=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-24-donation-ticket/tickets.png&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To raise enough amount of money required stably, We&amp;rsquo;re announcing another way to contribute on our event.&#xA;From today, You can contribute to our successful event by becoming one of our individual patrons!&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To become our patron, Visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://eventyay.com/e/75ac7f83&#34;&gt;our event page on eventyay.com&lt;/a&gt; and follow steps below.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Sign in with your eventyay.com account.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Scroll down to &amp;ldquo;Tickets&amp;rdquo; section, You will see &amp;ldquo;Sign Up to Join Ubucon Asia 2021&amp;rdquo; which is free ticket and &amp;ldquo;Donation Ticket&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set price of donation ticket you would like to donate. (You can set amount between 50 USD ~ 500 USD)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Set quantity of donation ticket. And Click &amp;ldquo;Order now&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On next screen, fill in the &amp;ldquo;Ticket Holder&amp;rsquo;s Information&amp;rdquo; form. If you need, Check &amp;ldquo;Enable Billing Information&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On &amp;ldquo;Payment Method&amp;rdquo; choose Paypal. (which is the only payment option you will found) and then click &amp;ldquo;Proceed to Checkout&amp;rdquo; to continue&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;On next screen, confirm payment information. Then Click the yellow &amp;ldquo;Pay with PayPal&amp;rdquo; button.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;You should now see PayPal payment dialog. (On bottom, You should be able to see &amp;ldquo;Cancel and return to FOSSASIA PTE. LTD.&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To make payment, Sign in with your PayPal account to make payment, or just choose &amp;ldquo;Pay with a Card&amp;rdquo; to pay without PayPal account.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;After succesful payment, you will be able to download invoice, see payment result, and cancel order in case if you want.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ol&gt;&#xA;&lt;blockquote&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;To purchase donation ticket, You will need a debit or credit card that PayPal supports.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Proposals</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-30-calling-for-proposals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:39:21 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-30-calling-for-proposals/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;UbuCon Asia 2021 team have been calling for speakers, volunteers, sponsors and community partners from earlier this month.&#xA;As this is the first time to organize UbuCon Asia, Our proposal period is relatively longer then other conferences.&#xA;This is a reminder post that includes all details for each items and URL link to them.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;calling-for-speakers&#34;&gt;Calling for speakers&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Submit until June 30th 2021, Session acceptance will be on July 30th 2021&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Session type: Talk(30min, 45min), Lightning talk(5min), Workshop(1hour, 2hour), Panel duscussions(55mins)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;All session duration includes time for question and answer&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;For &amp;ldquo;Talk&amp;rdquo; type session, you can submit pre-recorded session. You still exprected to present on the room on your session time to answer questions from attendees.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;For pre-recorded talks, You can submit session in Korean, Japanese, Chinese(China), Chinese(Taiwan), Cantonese(Hong Kong) and Indonesia&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../2021-05-05-call-for-speakers&#34;&gt;See Calling for speakers details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/cfs/&#34;&gt;Submit your session on eventyay.com - Sign up/Sign in for eventyay.com required&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://wiki.ubuntu.com/UbuconAsia/2021/SessionIdeas&#34;&gt;Session topic ideas that might help you to choose topic&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Inquiries: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:content@ubucon.asia&#34;&gt;content@ubucon.asia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;calling-for-video-translation-volunteers&#34;&gt;Calling for video translation volunteers&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Submit until June 30th 2021, Application result will be announced on July 30th 2021&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Help us to translate Non-English pre-recorded session into English&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Languages: Korean, Japanese, Chinese(China), Chinese(Taiwan), Cantonese(Hong Kong) and Indonesia&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;We&amp;rsquo;ll use some automation tools (Speech to text, Translation API) to automate our jobs.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;../2021-05-05-calling-for-translation-volunteers&#34;&gt;See Calling for translation volunteers details&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://forms.gle/3qJwwiKdKsUTKFLB8&#34;&gt;Submit volunteer application&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Inquiries: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:contact@ubucon.asia&#34;&gt;contact@ubucon.asia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;calling-for-sponsors&#34;&gt;Calling for sponsors&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Although it&amp;rsquo;s a fully virtual event, We still need help from sponsors to make this event actually happen.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Become our sponsor, and let&amp;rsquo;s shape out the first UbuCon Asia event!&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/&#34;&gt;See sponsorship program details and sponsorship brochure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Contact us to become our sponsor: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:sponsorship@ubucon.asia&#34;&gt;sponsorship@ubucon.asia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;calling-for-partner-communities&#34;&gt;Calling for partner communities&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;To promote UbuCon Asia event across Asia much further, We’re looking for partner communities.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Your community will collaborate with UbuCon Asia team to cross-promote each other’s community and event.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/join-as-partner-community/&#34;&gt;See partner community program details and brochure&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Contact us to become our partner community: &lt;a href=&#34;mailto:contact@ubucon.asia&#34;&gt;contact@ubucon.asia&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Video Translation Volunteers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-calling-for-translation-volunteers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 12:01:51 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-calling-for-translation-volunteers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;As we begin &lt;a href=&#34;../2021-05-05-call-for-speakers&#34;&gt;calling for speakers&lt;/a&gt;, We&amp;rsquo;re now also calling for translation volunteers from today.&#xA;Translation volunteers will colloborate local community to &lt;strong&gt;translate pre-recorded sessions from following languages to English.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Korean - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Korea Community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Japanese - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Japanese Community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chinese(China) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu China Community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Chinese(Taiwan) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Taiwan Community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Cantonese(Hong Kong) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Hong Kong Community&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Indonesian - You will collaborate GNOME Indonesia and Openstack Indonesia&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We will use speech-to-text and machine translation tool to automate subtitle works. But there will be still many things to fix. therefore, help from volunteers are still required.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Speakers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-call-for-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 09:50:20 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-call-for-speakers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The first Ubuntu Conference in Asia (Ubucon Asia 2021) is four months ahead!&#xA;Ubucon Asia 2021 Call for Speakers is now open until 30 June, and talks acceptance will be on 30 July.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s the reference topics for you to discuss in Ubucon Asia 2021:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Desktop&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Server/Infrastructure/Cloud&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Windows Subsystem for Linux(WSL)&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Localization(L10n)/Fonts/Input Methods&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Internet of Things(IoT)/Embedded&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Security&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Community/Social Context&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;Case Studies&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;etc.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;We have some sessions to talk with two days event. We usually recommend to give presentation in English. But GOOD NEWS if you are not confident with your English, for Talks and Panels you may consider to give presentation in following languages (Korean, Japanese, Chinese(China), Chinese(Taiwan), Cantonese(Hong Kong), Indonesia).&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Ubucon Asia 2021 Plan updates</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-04-21-some-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:10:16 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-04-21-some-updates/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s been about 3 months after I published post &lt;a href=&#34;../2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers&#34;&gt;&amp;ldquo;Looking for organizers&amp;rdquo;&lt;/a&gt;.&#xA;Last 3 months, many Ubuntu Local communities and other FLOSS communities contact me to join Ubucon Asia 2021 team.&#xA;Today, We have 12 host communities from 10 different regions in the team. Some organizers from those communities with excellent experience with organizing international events also joined our team.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;And with this Ubucon Asia 2021 team, We&amp;rsquo;ve been made many progress until now. Today I would like to share some planned schedules of upcoming Ubucon Asia 2021.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Looking for organizers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 01:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In Asia, You can find various community conferences about open source and linux that covers Asia region. Good examples of this are:&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;openSUSE.Asia&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;GNOME.Asia&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;LibreOffice Asia Conference&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;PyCon APAC&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;FOSSASIA Summit&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;and more&amp;hellip;&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;For past a few years, when I was the leader of Ubuntu Korea Community, I attended several conferences overseas to not just meet and learn but also to interact with Ubuntu local communities overseas. Especially, communities located near South Korea region.&#xA;By attending overseas events, I could interact with people from various open source communities from manu different regions.&#xA;But, Unfortunately, I could rarely meet people from Ubuntu local communities. Also, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find Ubuntu conference or event for Asia region.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
