<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on Ubucon Asia 2021</title>
    <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on Ubucon Asia 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 20:00:00 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ubucon Asia 2021 - YouTube Premiere Restream - 9-10 Oct, 2021</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-10-05-restream-schedule/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Oct 2021 20:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-10-05-restream-schedule/</guid>
      <description>Thank you once again to everyone who took part in the first Ubucon Asia 2021.
Thank you so much to our speakers, who spent a great deal of time preparing their wonderful presentations. For anyone who missed any of them, or would like to watch them again, we are announcing that they will be restreamed on YouTube on 9-10 Oct 2021 and will thereafter be available to watch on demand. Details are below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National IT Industry Promotion Agency of Korea (NIPA) is a Bronze Sponsor for Ubucon Asia 2021!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-18-nipa-kr-bronze-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Sep 2021 14:49:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-18-nipa-kr-bronze-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We are proud to announce that the National IT Industry Promotion Agency of Korea (NIPA) is a Bronze Sponsor for Ubucon Asia 2021!
NIPA is a national organisation in Korea that actively supports and promotes open source software development. It strengthens software development and provides industry support in a multitude of ways.
NIPA is devoted to reinforcing the competitiveness of the ICT industry and contributes to national economic growth through efficient support and laying the groundwork for industrial technology promotion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft has joined as a Gold Sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-08-microsoft-joins-as-gold-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2021 20:49:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-08-microsoft-joins-as-gold-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We are proud to announce Microsoft as a Gold Sponsor for Ubucon Asia 2021.
Microsoft requires no introduction in the technology world.
Azure cloud, hybrid cloud and on-premise technologies are leaders in software as a service (SaaS), platform as a service (PaaS) and infrastructure as a service (IaaS).
Did you know that Ubuntu-based workloads are among the fastest growing on Microsoft Azure? Their partnership with Canonical has delivered an Azure-optimized kernel, improved performance, advanced security, automatic patching and updates, and flexible pricing options for Ubuntu on Azure as well as open source communities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Networking on Gather Town space</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-05-networking-on-gather-town/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2021 23:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-09-05-networking-on-gather-town/</guid>
      <description>Hi everyone! The first UbuCon Asia coming in less then a month!
On this first UbuCon Asia, We&amp;rsquo;ll also have an additional virtual space: Gather Town space We&amp;rsquo;ll use both Eventyay and Gather Town.
 Eventyay for ticketing, timetable, video conference calls and Sponsor/Partner Community information page(Exhibition page) Gather Town space for Virtual booth(for sponsors and partner communities) and Networking between attendees!  Since we made decision on this very recently, Other then Virtual booth details, We don&amp;rsquo;t have plans on other details yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cloudmate joins as our Silver sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-08-10-cloudmate-joins-as-silver-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 01:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-08-10-cloudmate-joins-as-silver-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We are gladly to announce Cloudmate as our part of Silver Sponsor.
Cloudmate is an certified CSP(Cloud Service Provider) company in Seoul, South Korea. They provides professional managed service on cloud environment. Based on experiences from MNCs, Cloudmate has its best certified engineers and developers in the cloud sector. Through the professional managed service, Cloudmate supports systematic management and its cloud infrastructure to the customers. Furthermore, Cloudmate also offers consulting for cloud service to industries that are adapting cloud infrastructure for the first time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello UbuCon Asia speakers!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-30-speaker-schedules/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 12:47:39 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-30-speaker-schedules/</guid>
      <description>Hello UbuCon Asia 2021 speakers! Thanks again for submitting your proposals for the first UbuCon Asia! We just completed reviewing proposals and now reaching out each person to confirm speaker participation.
Confirm your participation If your proposal was accepted, We&amp;rsquo;ll send you an email to confirm whether you&amp;rsquo;ll give speech on the event. You may also check eventyay to see whether your proposal was accepted. To confirm your speaker participation, simply reply us and tell us you will participate as speaker.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thank you to Ubuntu for Join as Diamond Sponsor!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-24-ubuntu-joins-as-diamond-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2021 01:49:00 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-24-ubuntu-joins-as-diamond-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>We are gladly to announce Ubuntu as our part of Diamond Sponsor.
The Ubuntu desktop as we know is the world&amp;rsquo;s most widely used Linux workstation platform, powering the work of engineers across the globe. Ubuntu today has many flavours and dozens of specialized derivatives. All share common infrastructure and software, making Ubuntu a unique single platform that scales from consumer electronics to the desktop and up into the cloud for enterprise computing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for speakers is now closed!</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-15-cfs-is-now-closed/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 00:22:07 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-15-cfs-is-now-closed/</guid>
      <description>Hello folks! Calling for speakers is now closed!
Thanks to everyone who submitted session proposals to the first Ubuntu conference in Asia! We have received total 46 proposals! This includes&amp;hellip;
 Talks &amp;amp; Extended Talks Lightning talks Workshops Panel discussions  But this does not includes social events and sponsor sessions yet. In next 2 weeks, Our content team will review your submissions until the end of this month. Content team folks may contact to each person who submitted proposals to ask some further details.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Double check your proposal submissions before deadline</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-11-double-check-proposal-submission/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Jul 2021 15:34:54 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-07-11-double-check-proposal-submission/</guid>
      <description>Call for speakers will close soon on July 14th 23:59 UTC+9! If you have submitted any session proposals, please double check your submissions and update it if required before the deadline comes.
Your speaker info Please see the image and description below and check your speaker info submissions once again to see if anything missing.
 Name: Your full name (e.g. Youngbin Han) Email: Your email contact address. You&amp;rsquo;ll receive proposal review result with the email address you entered here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for proposals extended by July 14</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-30-cfp-extended-by-july-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2021 08:31:29 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-30-cfp-extended-by-july-14/</guid>
      <description>If you have been rush into submitting proposal, You now have extra 2 more weeks to finalize submitting your proposlas! UbuCon Asia 2021 Calling for proposal due date has been extended by July 14th 23:59 (UTC+9).
For your informations, See details you need know from below before submitting proposals. Please do not hesitate to contact Ubucon Asia team whether through social media or email if you are not sure about writing your proposal or preparing your presentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become our individual patron today</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-24-donation-ticket/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Jun 2021 00:20:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-06-24-donation-ticket/</guid>
      <description>To raise enough amount of money required stably, We&amp;rsquo;re announcing another way to contribute on our event. From today, You can contribute to our successful event by becoming one of our individual patrons!
To become our patron, Visit our event page on eventyay.com and follow steps below.
 Sign in with your eventyay.com account. Scroll down to &amp;ldquo;Tickets&amp;rdquo; section, You will see &amp;ldquo;Sign Up to Join Ubucon Asia 2021&amp;rdquo; which is free ticket and &amp;ldquo;Donation Ticket&amp;rdquo; Set price of donation ticket you would like to donate.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Proposals</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-30-calling-for-proposals/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 22:39:21 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-30-calling-for-proposals/</guid>
      <description>UbuCon Asia 2021 team have been calling for speakers, volunteers, sponsors and community partners from earlier this month. As this is the first time to organize UbuCon Asia, Our proposal period is relatively longer then other conferences. This is a reminder post that includes all details for each items and URL link to them.
Calling for speakers  Submit until June 30th 2021, Session acceptance will be on July 30th 2021 Session type: Talk(30min, 45min), Lightning talk(5min), Workshop(1hour, 2hour), Panel duscussions(55mins) All session duration includes time for question and answer For &amp;ldquo;Talk&amp;rdquo; type session, you can submit pre-recorded session.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Video Translation Volunteers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-calling-for-translation-volunteers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 12:01:51 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-calling-for-translation-volunteers/</guid>
      <description>As we begin calling for speakers, We&amp;rsquo;re now also calling for translation volunteers from today. Translation volunteers will colloborate local community to translate pre-recorded sessions from following languages to English.
 Korean - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Korea Community Japanese - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Japanese Community Chinese(China) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu China Community Chinese(Taiwan) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Taiwan Community Cantonese(Hong Kong) - You will collaborate with Ubuntu Hong Kong Community Indonesian - You will collaborate GNOME Indonesia and Openstack Indonesia  We will use speech-to-text and machine translation tool to automate subtitle works.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling for Speakers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-call-for-speakers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 09:50:20 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-05-05-call-for-speakers/</guid>
      <description>The first Ubuntu Conference in Asia (Ubucon Asia 2021) is four months ahead! Ubucon Asia 2021 Call for Speakers is now open until 30 June, and talks acceptance will be on 30 July.
Here&amp;rsquo;s the reference topics for you to discuss in Ubucon Asia 2021:
 Desktop Server/Infrastructure/Cloud Windows Subsystem for Linux(WSL) Localization(L10n)/Fonts/Input Methods Internet of Things(IoT)/Embedded Security Community/Social Context Case Studies etc.  We have some sessions to talk with two days event.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubucon Asia 2021 Plan updates</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-04-21-some-updates/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2021 00:10:16 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-04-21-some-updates/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been about 3 months after I published post &amp;ldquo;Looking for organizers&amp;rdquo;. Last 3 months, many Ubuntu Local communities and other FLOSS communities contact me to join Ubucon Asia 2021 team. Today, We have 12 host communities from 10 different regions in the team. Some organizers from those communities with excellent experience with organizing international events also joined our team.
And with this Ubucon Asia 2021 team, We&amp;rsquo;ve been made many progress until now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Looking for organizers</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jan 2021 01:00:00 +0900</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/news/2021-01-07-looking-for-organizers/</guid>
      <description>In Asia, You can find various community conferences about open source and linux that covers Asia region. Good examples of this are:
 openSUSE.Asia GNOME.Asia LibreOffice Asia Conference PyCon APAC FOSSASIA Summit and more&amp;hellip;  For past a few years, when I was the leader of Ubuntu Korea Community, I attended several conferences overseas to not just meet and learn but also to interact with Ubuntu local communities overseas. Especially, communities located near South Korea region.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
