<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sponsors on Ubucon Asia 2021</title>
    <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sponsors on Ubucon Asia 2021</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>.NET DEV</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/dotnetdevkr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/dotnetdevkr/</guid>
      <description> .Net Dev is a local .Net user group in South Korea. Our community members are especially interested in .NET development and its ecosystem.  Including ASP.NET, EF, Blazor, etc&amp;hellip;   We runs regular local conference called &amp;ldquo;.NET Conf x Seoul&amp;rdquo; every year and &amp;ldquo;.NET Conf Mini&amp;rdquo; almost every quarter. .NET Conf Korea by .NET Dev: https://dotnetconf.kr .NET Medium Blog: https://blog.dotnetdev.kr .NET Dev Discourse: https://forum.dotnetdev.kr  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Become a sponsor</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/become-a-sponsor/</guid>
      <description>Thank you for your interest in Ubuntu and Ubucon Asia.
As a non-profit and community organized event, Even Ubucon Asia 2021 is fully virtual event, We still need support from sponsors to make the event happen.
By becoming one of our sponsors, you are directly contributing to research and development of Ubuntu and Open Source Software, and also making Open Source Community more active and sustainable.
Your contribution makes it possible for us to bring a large number of Ubuntu users and contributors across Asia to connect, interact, help and learn together.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gimpscape ID</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/gimpscape-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/gimpscape-id/</guid>
      <description>Gimpscape ID community is a one of design community from Indonesia that has oriented to the use of Free/Open Source Software (FOSS). On various occasions, Gimpscape ID always strives to contribute to activities related to free/open source software.
 Telegram https://t.me/gimpscape Instagram https://instagram/gimpscape_id  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join as Partner Community</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/join-as-partner-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/join-as-partner-community/</guid>
      <description>To promote UbuCon Asia event across Asia much further, We’re looking for partner communities. By becoming our partner community, Your community will collaborate with UbuCon Asia team to cross-promote each other’s community and event. This will be a big help for both partner communities and UbuCon Asia to connect with even more diverse people and encourage them to participate and engage.
To learn more about our partner community program, please refer to our brochure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>KLAS (Kelompok Linux Arek Suroboyo)</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/klas/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/klas/</guid>
      <description>Arek Suroboyo Linux Group (Surabaya Linux User Group) (KLAS) is one of the Linux user groups in the city of Surabaya. We have been around since 1995, and are still active today. We have several routine agendas and facilities that we do and until now we have facilitated them to support Go FOSS activities in Surabaya, such as:
 Cangkrukan KLAS Local Conferences (Open Infrastucture Day 2019) International Conferences (openSUSE.Asia Summit 2019, GNOME.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>OpenStack Korea User Group</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/openstack-kr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/openstack-kr/</guid>
      <description>OpenStack is cloud operating system which can manage massive computing in data center, storage, network resource and provisioning by APIs. As an official user group, OpenStack Korea Community actively engages with many OpenStack users and interested people through various communication channels such as Facebook, mailing list, IRC, and Slack (sign up), as well as various regular seminars, study activities, and translation team activities. OpenStack Korea Community held 1st OpenStack Day Korea event in 2014, and has held events every year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ubuntu Kylin</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-kylin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/ubuntu-kylin/</guid>
      <description>Ubuntu Kylin is an official flavor of Ubuntu. It committed to bringing an easy, excellent, expert, and elaborate Linux distribution to users worldwide. It integrates the independently developed UKUI desktop environment which adheres to the friendly and simple design, aka Ubuntu Kylin User Interface. It includes more than 20 applications developed for ordinary users to enjoy a pleasant life and easy office operating system experience.  Links to social media</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WSLHUB (WSL Korea User Group)</title>
      <link>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/wslhub/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2021.ubucon.asia/sponsors/wslhub/</guid>
      <description> WSLHUB is a local user group community in South Korea. Our community members are especially interested in WSL and the Linux Ecosystem. Our community currently runs several open-source projects(such as WslManager, WslQuery) and a Facebook group to communicate with our members.  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
